<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  
  <XST_Lirosa.label>Lirosa</XST_Lirosa.label>
  <XST_Lirosa.description>(Lirosa's attitude towards the colony is between original Cassandra and Phoebe, she prefers peace development and trading between factions.)

&lt;color=#00970e&gt;&lt;b&gt;Jaeger&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;
There was once a space pirate group whose targets were not villages, but other pirate forces. They devoured these groups and reorganized them, slowly becoming a military force. After massive expansion, they became an unstoppable force, constantly pillaging. Due to their quick and safe method of earning money, they attracted a large number of people. Eventually, they could only rob those who could no longer sustain their huge organization. They began to reform and evolve, eventually becoming the Jaeger we know today.

The social structure of the Jaeger is very simple and only divided into three classes: soldiers, workers, and slaves. The soldiers include all combat units and officers, while the workers consist of all production and trade-related personnel. The slaves are the people and their descendants from conquered areas who are treated as property by the Jaeger. Their social status, apart from that of slaves, is basically the same and their income is distributed by the military government. The Jaeger have abandoned the system of leaders and are now governed by a military government composed of seven generals. Except for financial and major decisions, they have the autonomy to make individual decisions in their respective domains and territories. There is no term limit, and if a general resigns or passes away, their superior will take over their position. The Jaeger also have an independent military court to regulate the behavior of soldiers.

The Jaeger have a wide range of economic sources which includes arms trading, drug trafficking, and slave trading. Among them, the services of mercenaries and special mission contracts are particularly popular because they do not concern themselves with reasons or morals, nor do they consider politics or diplomacy. They only consider the danger of the mission and the amount of money involved. As long as there is detailed mission information and sufficient funds, the employer will have a powerful army at their disposal. The Jaeger also resort to any means necessary to seize markets and production lines, however, this behavior has sparked numerous rebellions, with Diamond Bone being their biggest enemy.

Although the Jaeger have been highly regulated, their essence is still that of pirates. Commanders would allow soldiers to burn, kill and loot after capturing a stronghold, and even the military court tolerates these actions. Therefore, in the eyes of other forces, the Jaeger are nothing more than a mutated pirate gang. This has led to their foreign relations being consistently unfavorable. In such circumstances, young officers believe that the operating methods of the Jaeger need to change. They have organized a group called the "Peace Messenger", hoping to gradually change the outside world's perception of them.

&lt;color=#00970e&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lirosa&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;
Lirosa was born into a military family of the Jaeger. Her parents were a handsome man and a beautiful woman. Her father was a war hero known as the "Eagle Eye," while her mother was a torturer. Her father originally belonged to the resistance army, but joined the Jaeger after meeting her mother. Lirosa also has a twin sister named Evan, who looks very different from their family and is considered ugly. Their father told her that it was due to genetic defects that made Evan look like that and warned her not to harm her sister. Lirosa never had such thoughts because even though Evan looked ugly, she was very intelligent. She could understand how things worked just by looking at them and was like a genius, making her an idol for Lirosa.

Since their birth, their mother resigned from her position as a torturer and took care of them most of the time because their father was often away due to military duties. Their mother had originally planned for Lirosa to become a welfare officer when she grew up since she was kind-hearted and empathetic even towards insects that she couldn't bear to kill. However, one day, when Lirosa was 5 years old, her mother found out that she had stolen her father's sniper rifle to shoot at targets and was hitting every shot with precision. It was then that her mother realized that she was not an ordinary child.

Due to being from a military family and being beautiful and talented, Lirosa was forced to become a key training project, while Evan, despite being intelligent, was ignored due to her lack of physical abilities. Everything that Lirosa possessed made Evan very envious, and Lirosa, feeling guilty about this, promised to make her the chief of staff when she grew up. Evan was delighted to hear this and worked hard to fulfill this promise. Seeing Evan's intelligence and aptitude in intellectual tasks, their mother decided to send her to study at the Star Explorer's Academy when she was older.

When Lirosa was 7 years old, their mother decided to take Evan with her to the Star Explorer's Academy for enrollment procedures. Before they left, she hugged Evan goodbye, but little did they know that it would be their final farewell. Their mother and Evan's travel party were attacked by the Diamond Bone forces on the way, and all of the soldiers escorting them were killed. Both of them went missing from that day onwards. During that time, Lirosa saw her father continuously blaming himself for what happened, and she tried to comfort him, but the situation only got worse. Eventually, their father resigned from his position as an instructor and locked himself in his room all day. Lirosa became very worried, but she still believed that there would be a miracle because in her heart, Evan and their mother were still alive.

After a few years, a FedEx courier arrived at their home with a handmade and exquisite sofa. Lirosa didn't understand why it was delivered to them, so she placed it in the living room. Unexpectedly, their father burst into tears when he saw the sofa, muttering to himself incessantly. Lirosa knew something was wrong and sought help from a doctor and their father's friends. After receiving psychological counseling and comfort, their father became calmer, started to recover, and began talking to Lirosa again. However, this change made Lirosa even more uneasy because she knew that there must be some problem with the sofa. Nevertheless, she didn't dare to ask about it to prevent her father from getting upset again.

Finally, one day, Lirosa saw her father measuring the sofa using a ruler. She finally asked him why he was doing that, but her father ignored her. A few days later, her father gave her a winged emblem and told her to find her sister. He then sat on the sofa and committed suicide with a gun.

After losing her parents, Lirosa was assigned to live and study at a military officer training facility by the government. Many officers showed her special care due to her father's reputation, and her shooting talent was demonstrated during her time at the training facility. At only 14 years old, she went from being a trainee to becoming a sniper training officer, with some officers even praising her skills as surpassing those of her father.

Lirosa served as a training officer for less than a year before voluntarily requesting to be deployed to the front lines in response to the resistance army's attack on the Jaegers. This decision was made by Lirosa herself, and not at the military's request. She knew that staying in the restrictive training facility would keep the winged emblem her father gave her forever a mystery.

The reality of the battlefield was vastly different from what Lirosa had imagined. She used to think that getting shot meant just falling down and bleeding, but on the front lines, the scenes were filled with carnage and gore from heavy artillery fire. After experiencing the baptism of war, she became serious and silent. She knew that any mistake could mean failing to fulfill her father's dying wish.

After participating in over a dozen battles as a sniper, Lirosa achieved a terrifying record. Her fearsome reputation did not come from how many people she killed, but rather from her zero-kill record. When faced with the enemy, Lirosa found that she couldn't bring herself to take a life. Each time before pulling the trigger, she would think about her mother and Evan. With one movement of her finger, the enemy's family would suffer the same fate. She decided to effectively stop their actions without killing them, becoming known as the terrifying Knee-Destroyer. Her god-like spatial awareness, predictive ability, dynamic vision, and four-dimensional bladder, combined with her father's double-tap sniper technique, made her capable of bringing down enemies in any position, whether walking, running, crawling, or even riding heavy machinery. She even caused some enemies to wear helmets on their knees from fear of her.

Due to this incident, Lirosa quickly became a sensation and was subsequently used for propaganda by the military. She was referred to as the "Queen" who made enemies kneel, as her cold and stern demeanor perfectly suited the title. This nickname spread quickly, causing panic among the resistance army whenever they learned that the Queen had arrived. Some even fell to their knees in fear of being shot in the knee. However, these immobilized casualties and soldiers posed a significant resource drain and psychological burden on the resistance army. The frequent complaints of those shot in the knee - "I can only be a guard in the future" - filled the entire army with fear. As time passed, most of them lost their will to fight and surrendered, and the war turned into sporadic conflicts.

At the end of the war, the military's official media heavily promoted Lirosa as the one who quelled the war in two years, and at the age of 17, she was honored as a war hero and referred to as the "Queen" by others. From then on, Lirosa enjoyed the treatment of a hero, receiving a fixed monthly bonus and having the freedom to choose to participate in various missions and military affairs.

Afterwards, Lirosa chose to join the "Peace Messenger", an organization established to change the public's perception of Jaegers. It was primarily responsible for public relations work and also conducted charitable activities. The organization had flexible working hours, which suited her nature better, and more importantly, she could gather a lot of information while working. At this point, Lirosa could finally focus on investigating the Winged Emblem. Unfortunately, things were not so simple. Although she spent most of her bonus on intelligence gathering and even came into contact with XEO assassins, no one knew the source of this mysterious emblem. The only thing left uninvestigated was the hostile Diamond Bone force. Due to the military government's sensitivity to Diamond Bone-related matters, mishandling it could lead to being treated as a spy. Originally, Lirosa hoped to find other entry points, but it seemed impossible. After careful consideration, she unilaterally leaked information about the emblem to Diamond Bone and secretly observed them.

A few weeks later, a lone member of the resistance army appeared on the Jaeger's border. His sniping was so precise that he was able to shoot two consecutive shots, hitting his targets in places that were too gruesome to look at. Men were shot in their testicles or had their heads blown off, while women had their breasts and genitals shot, rendering them sterile even if they managed to survive. This terrifying style of shooting immediately reminded people of the late sharpsniper Eagle Eye, who happened to be Lirosa's father. However, since Eagle Eye had already passed away, the military believed that someone was imitating him to affect the morale of the troops. As time went on, the situation became increasingly serious. The enemy's strength was almost on par with that of Eagle Eye, causing a large number of casualties among the soldiers. Despite the Jaeger's daily bombing, it had no effect, leaving the military with no choice but to order the female soldiers to retreat from the border first.

Although the military made efforts to suppress the spread of the incident, Lirosa quickly obtained intelligence from her role as a Peace Messenger. She believed that the sniper must be connected to her father and offered to fight for the cause, but the military refused to let her participate, fearing it would damage their image if the "Queen" were insulted. In the end, Lirosa had to exercise her hero's right to demand permission from the local general to fight. Moved by her determination, the general agreed, but the risks of sniper ambushes were high due to the unpredictability of the battlefield. If anything unexpected happened, the general could not explain it to the other six generals. Therefore, he proposed a condition to Lirosa: if the opponent agreed to a duel, she could fight. Soon after, the border troops broadcasted the rules of the duel. If the opponent fired two shots in succession, it would mean they agreed to the duel. As a result, the soldier holding the loudspeaker and the officer leading the troops both became eunuchs. The soldiers who knew about the upcoming battle between the "Queen" and "Eagle Eye" were filled with excitement, causing the local popcorn and soda stocks to sell out instantly.

Before the duel, both parties presented their demands and received agreement from each other. The mysterious sniper requested that if he won, the Jaeger would return the territory and promise never to attack again. The Jaeger, on the other hand, demanded complete dissolution of the resistance army and submission to the military government. The rules of the duel were very simple: only the Red Line rifle provided by the committee could be used, and the contestants could only wear leather or cloth armor. Both parties had to stand at attention holding their rifles and be ready at a distance of 100 meters apart on the plain. They could only begin shooting after the signal was given. The duel would continue until one side died or lost the ability to fight, and the winner would have the right to execute the defeated opponent. The stakes were high for Lirosa, as the mysterious sniper had already threatened to kill the "Queen" and disrupt morale. However, having lost everything, she didn't care about the risks. She only focused on her father's last words that her sister might still be alive, and this opponent was the key. Therefore, winning was imperative for her.

Finally, the day of the duel had arrived. The vast plain was packed with onlookers, and there were more members of the resistance army who had surrendered than there were Jaeger soldiers present. During the war, many members of the resistance army understood that they could easily be killed by a mere shot from Queen Lirosa's gun, and that she could take them out one by one. However, instead of killing them, she aimed for their knees which saved them during the brutal battles. Despite their fear of the Queen, the resistance army deeply appreciated this female hero. Many of those who had been shot in the knees even volunteered to maintain order and guard the area, all for the chance to catch a glimpse of the legendary Queen.

Due to concerns for the safety of their heroes, the military government strictly prohibited the release of any related images or photos. In sniper situations, Lirosa was essentially a legend, and some even speculated that the knee damage was not caused by a single sniper. Such speculation only increased people's curiosity about her. The military government also recognized the resistance army's view towards Lirosa, which is why they allowed her to appear in public with her true identity. They even built temporary spectator stands for the unprecedented number of viewers present in order to change their perception of the government.

On that day, Lirosa appeared in a tight-fitting grey and black leather suit, causing a commotion throughout the audience. No one had expected the queen who joined the military to be such an exquisite beauty, and the military realized that allowing her to appear was worth it, as long as they could win this duel to achieve their goal. The mysterious sniper who followed Lirosa onto the field was much more plain, wearing a brown leather coat with a hooded headpiece to prevent future assassination attempts. As the two inspected their weapons on the open plain, the audience could see that Lirosa's outfit was highly disadvantageous for her, while the bulky leather coat of the mysterious sniper could serve to disrupt vision, causing them to secretly worry about Lirosa.

The two faced each other in the center of the field and shook hands. The mysterious sniper told Lirosa that he couldn't care less about her looks and would blow her away, but the cold-hearted Lirosa ignored him and walked back to her starting position. After they both prepared themselves, the whole arena fell silent. Lirosa's father had explained to her the key points of this shooting technique, which focused on consciousness and muscle movement during shooting. Therefore, as long as one predicts correctly when seeing the opponent, they can use micro movements to evade. The Eagle Eye imposter was also very aware of this, so he wore a leather jacket, which made it difficult for his hands and knees to be accurately observed. He even chose the body axis, which cannot make micro movements, as his shooting target.

As the signal gun went off, both sides raised their guns and fired a shot blindly. At that moment, the audience screamed as the Queen's breast was pierced from the side, causing a bunch of mosaic to burst out. Although Lirosa had predicted the hit location and dodged sideways, she could not escape being hit. The force of the bullet pulled her curvaceous body down to the ground. On the other hand, the mysterious sniper remained unharmed, only the weapon he held in his hand, which he could not avoid when aiming and attacking, was hit. Looking at the gun in his hand that had become trash, the mysterious sniper secretly admired Lirosa's intelligence and courage. However, one had no idea whether she was dead or alive, while the other had a weapon that had been shattered. As the military forces of the conference, they did not know how to judge the outcome for a while. The whole venue erupted in intense discussion, and the audience was worried about the Queen who had been pierced in the breast because the hollow effect of the Red Line rifle was notoriously powerful. From the mosaic on the ground, they knew the situation was very serious and there was a risk to her life at any time. 

However, the mysterious sniper, who had lost his weapon, was now cursing her shamelessness. The audience immediately felt ashamed of him and those concerned about the Queen's injury began to argue with him. The mysterious sniper kept arguing, but all he got in return were more curses. Even the resistance army started booing at him. Finally, unable to withstand the pressure, he turned off the mosaic effect. When the mosaic disappeared, the audience saw a bunch of bursting sponges. It turned out that Lirosa had padded her B-cup breasts into D-cups with padding. This is a trick she learned from some female soldiers who survived mysterious sniper attacks, the tight-fitting suit she wears is not just for looks, but in direct contrast to the concealment provided by the mysterious sniper's leather jacket, it actually causes opponents to make mistakes in their shooting calculations. After learning the truth, the angry and pleasantly surprised audience started to clamor for a rematch and showered the venue with popcorn and soft drinks. The military had a hard time calming down the audience's emotions, but eventually managed to do so and announced that the queen had won.

Lirosa had just recovered from a dangerous duel, spared the mysterious sniper and handed him over to the military for interrogation. The Queen also gave a gift to the resistance army, announcing that if they were willing to pay taxes to the government, the land would be returned to them and slavery abolished. They would also receive protection from the Jaeger. This was the victory agreement proposed by her to the government and something the "Peace Messenger" had always wanted to do. Upon hearing this, the resistance army was moved to tears and no longer had to kneel down due to getting shot in the knee.

After this incident, Lirosa's charisma made the military realize that cooperation, rather than war and power, may be a better choice. From then on, the Queen's reputation spread throughout the borderlands, and some villages even voluntarily joined the Jaeger. The government also changed its domestic rules to accommodate this development. Although many frontline soldiers still held onto their bandit-like thinking, and the problems left by the war could not be solved overnight, these things began to slowly change.

After Lirosa returned to the Peace Messenger, she was unable to contact the mysterious sniper due to the military's obstruction. Although she was very anxious about this, her duel had become a legend among the Jaeger, and she was quickly becoming known as the "Queen." Therefore, she did not want to further stimulate the military by taking action. Several weeks later, Lirosa received a notification from the government requesting that she take over the interrogation of the mysterious sniper. This sudden change left her filled with doubts until she saw her father alive in the interrogation room. Shocked by this revelation, Lirosa immediately proposed conditions to the military - no recording and isolation - which they surprisingly agreed to on the spot. They only asked her to submit a detailed report afterwards.

They were then arranged in a secret room, and the military handed Lirosa a bag before leaving and closing the door. Without saying a word, Lirosa took out her winged emblem. The mysterious sniper widened his eyes upon seeing it and took out an opposite winged emblem from the bag, forming a pair of wings. Lirosa realized that the knot in her heart was about to be untied.

During their conversation, Lirosa learned that the person in front of her was her uncle. He informed her that the family's genes had been altered, and so they were destined to have twins. He was the real "Eagle Eye," while Lirosa's father had only intentionally joined the Jaeger as a spy using his name. Eagle Eye told Lirosa that her parents truly loved each other, and after her father expressed his intentions, he stopped sending information. It was always him working alone to cover up the intelligence work. Although Eagle Eye had retired, he came back into the picture upon receiving news of the winged emblem and realizing that his brother had met with misfortune. He returned to prevent himself from being suspected.

When Lirosa asked about the sofa, the situation took a sudden turn for the worse. Her uncle seemed like a different person, his voice becoming low and solemn. He countered by asking if she found the sofa comfortable to sit on, and thereafter refused to answer any more questions about it. Finally, he admitted that he was uncertain about the whereabouts of Lirosa's sister and refused to disclose his organization, only insisting that Jaeger execute him publicly. At this point, Lirosa sensed that Eagle Eye was already consumed by a deep fear. Later, Lirosa reported everything truthfully to the military except for the genetic modifications. Although there were no major breakthroughs, the military was very satisfied, and in accordance with Eagle Eye's wishes, they executed him publicly.

In the following months, Lirosa conducted investigations into genetic modification and the phenomenon of Sofa. All the clues pointed to Diamond Bone, a mysterious and secretive faction. It was then that she finally discovered why her father and Eagle Eye were so terrified. Rumors had it that Diamond Bone turned the family members of traitors into Sofa as a warning. If the traitor did not die, they would continue to turn their loved ones into Sofa until there were no more left. Lirosa's father had committed suicide to protect her from this fate. Upon realizing this, she returned home and wept in her mother(Sofa), vowing to find her sister.

One day, a few months later, Lirosa received information that a doctor was offering all of his assets to hire mercenaries. Intrigued, she hurried to the scene and saw that the doctor was not offering a small sum of money. However, he was still desperately seeking a six-person team. Lirosa was full of questions and asked the military personnel on duty to find out that he wanted to attack a Diamond Bone laboratory. Without any mission intelligence, no one was willing to join. Puzzled, Lirosa personally asked the doctor for more information and explained the difficulties, but he remained tight-lipped as if hiding something. Lirosa's intuition told her that there might be news about her sister in the laboratory, so she volunteered. Many soldiers flocked to join after seeing the Queen's involvement, and they eventually formed a 12-member squad. They formed a travel team and arrived at their destination a few days later. However, after reconnaissance, they realized that the situation was perilous. All of the laboratory guards were warriors wearing platinum power armor, and they also found XEO assassins, with a minimum of 90 people. 

Lirosa decided to cancel the mission and promised to return the doctor's hiring fee, compensating the team with her own reward. The doctor cried, saying that his daughter was doomed. Lirosa sympathized but understood the insurmountable difference in military strength, so she could only console the weeping father.

As they were preparing to return, they saw a white smoke rising on the horizon, accompanied by a series of shouts - "For the Queen" - which made Lirosa feel embarrassed and ashamed. Soon, a massive army appeared before her eyes. Apparently, her mission had been leaked, attracting a large number of troops to this location.

In the end, the Queen led a force of nearly 300 people to launch an attack. The battle did not last long, as some Diamond Bone soldiers began to panic and flee due to the overwhelming number of enemies, with only a few fanatical assassins still fighting. Diamond Bone soldiers began to burn down the laboratory and kill the researchers and test subjects. Seeing this, the Doctor became frantic and rushed into the lab. Lirosa could not stop him and could only follow in with over ten people. Screaming could be heard coming from the lab. Lirosa ordered them to prioritize finding the Doctor, but soon discovered that he had already died. Lirosa felt very sad and could only do her best to help the remaining people. However, the scene was chaotic, and the Diamond Bone soldiers did not even notice them, just slaughtering the test subjects and committing suicide. Lirosa's knee strikes were also ineffective, as they knelt down and committed suicide on the spot. The temperature at the scene also began to rise, so Lirosa ordered a retreat to protect the safety of her team members. After they left, the laboratory burned for several tens of minutes before collapsing.

Lirosa's unit only managed to save a few test subjects in the end, all of them being human-shaped pillows with their limbs removed. Lirosa approached them with a hopeful expression, inquiring about her sister's whereabouts, only to find that their vocal cords and teeth had been removed. They didn't even listen to Lirosa's words but continuously begged for death through their eyes and expressions. Lirosa knew full well the practices of Jaeger, and that the military would not spend resources on providing prosthetics for these types of captives. Instead, they would be treated as entertainment items and sold, ultimately destined to be tortured to death by their buyers. Despite knowing the consequences of violating military regulations, Lirosa still forcibly rescued them because she wanted to know about her sister's whereabouts. At this moment, she realized her mistake. Although Lirosa understood the consequences of her actions, her error was driven by personal motives, and only she could put an end to this tragedy. On this day, the Queen finally broke the record of zero kills. The soldiers were shocked to see the queen's actions, as the consequences of disposing of captives privately are severe, and everyone was discussing it fervently.

The news of the queen breaking the record of zero kills quickly spread among the Jaeger. To everyone's surprise, this well-intentioned violation led soldiers from various regions to sign a petition to plead with their respective generals on behalf of the queen, leaving the generals shocked. Despite this, Lirosa knew she would receive heavy punishment from the military court. No one was saved during the mission, the employer had died, and she acquired no information about her sister. It left her feeling utterly defeated. Soon after, Lirosa received an invitation from the Seven Generals, the highest level of meeting within Jaeger. She knew it must have been related to the mission. That day, she entered the meeting room nervously, where only the Seven Generals were present, and no other officers. The atmosphere was so tense that it was suffocating. When the generals saw her, they stood up without saying a word and slowly walked toward her, kneeling down in front of her. Lirosa was startled, and stepped back until she exited the conference hall and slowly closed the door. One of the generals nervously kicked the door open and carried her back to the central seat in the hall. The other generals, sweating profusely from the scare, returned to their respective seats. As Lirosa gradually regained her composure, the eldest general began to slowly tell the story of the Jaeger.

Originally, the Jaeger was just a group of eight righteous hunters whose goal was to dismantle the space pirates and absorb and teach them to do good. To effectively manage the organization, they elected a leader. However, as the organization grew larger, they felt pressure due to the lack of management expertise. In addition, the recruits were mainly uneducated robbers with no culture, and their only source of income was through robbery. At this point, some members suggested dissolving the organization, but the leader, who had already succumbed to his own power, disagreed and resorted to piracy in order to maintain the organization. His behavior awakened the nature of the members and the organization soon turned from justice to evil. After many years, many forces were forced to submit to the massive power of the organization. The leader had lost control and proclaimed himself the "Pirate King". The other seven members conspired to kill him and then jointly managed the organization, proclaiming the abolition of the leader system. They thought they could improve the situation, but they were wrong. The leader's ideology had deeply rooted in them and could not be changed back. Dissolving the organization would be like releasing wild animals, so they had to establish rules and manage it. However, the fundamental problem still existed. During their discussions, someone suggested creating another "Pirate King", but they realized that what they needed was not a leader who led others, but a hero who made others reflect on themselves.

From then on, these seven people became hero makers. They searched for suitable candidates and secretly molded them into heroes to serve as spiritual leaders for the robbers and guide them back to righteousness. However, they found that this was not easy because they needed more than just suitable candidates. They needed to create heroes at appropriate timing. Therefore, they were only able to create heroes, but not super-heroes during their time. Thus, the seven decided to pass on their responsibilities to their successors and let them carry on the tradition.

Therefore, the generals had long known that Lirosa's father was a fake "Eagle Eye" and that her mother, who served as a torturer for "Eagle Eye," was also arranged by them. The spy mission actually helped them because they needed heroes - creating heroes was what they were supposed to do. That is why Lirosa's past actions and requests went smoothly. Originally, the generals strictly prohibited informing those involved in hero-making to prevent abuse of power and another "Pirate King" from emerging. Lirosa was able to learn about the top secret information because of her personality and influence. From the violation of military regulations in this incident, the generals saw that Lirosa could very likely become the superhero who would bring the entire Jaeger back on track. Therefore, they decided to inform her of the confidential information and made it clear that she was the highest decision-maker. They warned her not to engage in any activity that could endanger her life, and the punishment from the court was only symbolic - prohibiting her from participating in large-scale missions. Now, Lirosa knows that she is no longer living just for herself but also for the future of the entire Jaeger. This responsibility will eventually become an invisible shackle for her, and as someone who has lost her freedom, she may never find her sister again.

*Lirosa, who is naturally kind and serious, no longer participates in dangerous missions because she bears a huge responsibility. Therefore, her story is relatively mild and does not involve too much fighting.</XST_Lirosa.description>
  
  <XST_Vic.label>Vic</XST_Vic.label>
  <XST_Vic.description>(Vic's attitude towards the colony is like original Cassandra，and he prefers events happening in the world.)

&lt;color=#008aff&gt;&lt;b&gt;Star Explorer&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;
A highly influential faction, originally just a group of scientists who were persecuted by religion and politics. However, several of them possessed expertise in aerospace technology and extraterrestrial mining, and they led other scientists while also incorporating exiles who had been banished from elsewhere. They quickly developed into a high-tech organization and attracted numerous investors, ultimately forming what is now known as the Star Explorer.

The Star Explorer have evolved into a democratic country, with the Star Explorer Council serving as their core governing body. This council is composed of 48 members and one chairman, with each member serving a term of five years. All members are appointed and elected by citizens, and any decision must receive support from 27 or more members to pass. However, due to factors such as factional struggles and financial flows, the operation of the system appears fair on the surface but is actually quite dark.

The Star Explorers believe that knowledge is power, which is why they invest heavily in technological development and extraterrestrial exploration. They have also established the "Star Explorer Database" to collect and study technology. Additionally, they collaborate with other factions, including Diamond Bone.

The Star Explorer fully utilizes the economic value of their military assets and soldiers. They create chaos and incite conflicts among other factions, and then export weapons or send troops to target factions to increase their influence. This has always been the development strategy of the Star Explorer. However, this behavior has drawn the attention of XEO, who retaliated by targeting them and assassinating eight council members within a week. This incident directly led to the employment of Jaeger by the Star Explorer to suppress XEO in the long term.

To maintain social stability, the Star Explorer exiles serious criminals and their families to other regions. If military personnel or special police discover exiles who have returned within the Star Explorer's territory, they are authorized to execute them on the spot without reporting to their superiors. Some of the exiles, due to their hatred towards the Star Explorer, have formed the Flame Legion and launched attacks against the Star Explorer's strongholds, causing a large number of civilian casualties. The conflict between the Star Explorer and the Flame Legion has never ceased, and the population of exiles continues to increase. Some commentators believe that some politicians intentionally create threats to the Star Explorer to gain greater political leverage.

&lt;color=#008aff&gt;&lt;b&gt;Vic&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;
Vic's parents were both archaeologists, and his mother gave birth to him while on an archaeological expedition. Without even a birth certificate, Vic was raised by his parents who frequently moved for work and didn't have much time to take care of him. As compensation, they bought him lots of indie games to play with. Through these games, Vic learned many survival skills, but what interested him the most was "mining." He often sneaked into excavation sites when his parents weren't looking and dug away. Vic had good luck and often found special items, but he knew they were artifacts that could affect his parents' work, so he never took them.

One day, Vic dug up a black stone in the ruins of an ancient city. As he gazed at the stone, it seemed like his soul was sucked into it, which made him feel amazing. Breaking his own rule, he decided to take it with him.

For a long period after that, the archaeology team remained at the same site, seemingly searching for something. There were often some cool-looking people coming and going, whom Vic's parents told him were assassins, warning him not to provoke them.

Vic, who had been waiting for too long, became increasingly bored and secretly took out the black stone to observe it. He hadn't shown the stone to his parents yet because he was afraid of being scolded. As he gazed at the stone, Vic could feel that it had some kind of consciousness. He tried talking to the stone in his mind, and although it didn't respond, he felt like he understood what the stone was thinking. It was as if he were talking to himself. From then on, whenever Vic felt bored, he would talk to the stone. Because he followed his parents around and couldn't make friends, the stone became his only friend.

A few months later, the archaeology team arrived at a new excavation site. Vic's parents stayed in the campsite most of the time to plan their archaeological schedule and route. One day, Vic absentmindedly took out the black stone, but his parents were terrified when they noticed it. His father panicked and pulled out a metal box from his backpack, telling Vic to stand still and not move. Vic stood frozen in place, watching as his father closed his eyes, grabbed the stone, and placed it in the box.

Vic thought he would be scolded for taking out the stone, but to his surprise, his parents gave him a thumbs up and promised to settle down on the Star Explorer, no longer living the life of wandering archaeologists. Excited, Vic shouted in joy. At that moment, Vic realized that even though he had lost the stone, that "friend" seemed to still linger in his mind.

Not long after, Vic's parents became anxious and suggested the archaeological team pack up their gear and return to the Star Explorer as soon as possible. They spent the entire night organizing their travel group and set off the next morning. Unfortunately, disaster struck soon after they departed when they were attacked by the Flame Legion's troops. The guards were all killed, and the rest were either killed or captured. Vic was frightened and prayed that someone would come to rescue them. That night, a group of people came to their aid, but the situation quickly turned chaotic. Taking advantage of the chaos, Vic grabbed some food and fled. He became separated from his parents and returned to the territory of the Star Explorer alone.

At just five years old and without his parents, Vic was forced to survive on the streets and play games like playing PlayerUnknown's Battlegrounds (PUBG). After two years of living this harsh life, he was eventually taken into an orphanage by a welfare officer of the Star Explorer. Through the baptism of fire, Vic became filled with killing intent. The other orphans in the orphanage thought he was crazy and avoided him, and he never paid attention to anyone else either.

During his days at the orphanage, Vic saw a staggeringly ugly girl being bullied every day by a group of people, including the guards who turned a blind eye. Although Vic had thought about intervening, the bullies were all tall young men and there were too many of them. His two years of playing PUBG taught him not to get involved in such situations. However, one day, the group began physically assaulting the girl after verbally abusing her, and eventually, she lost an eye and was close to death. The guards did nothing but hold melons instead of sticks. Unable to bear it any longer, Vic finally stepped in front of the girl and ordered the big guys to stop. The young men were initially hesitant, but they followed suit and started attacking him as well. Vic had no choice but to fight back against ten people. However, reality proved to be cruel, and he ended up in the hospital for three months after being hit on the head with a glass bottle and a watermelon. He couldn't remember anything after that and was questioned by the police. The doctors believed it was likely a concussion and told him not to worry.

After Vic recovered, he wasn't sent back to the orphanage. The reason was due to the fight at the orphanage. The judge sentenced him to attend a military school for training to give back to society, as he had caused serious injury and accidental death. Years later, Vic graduated from the military school with excellent grades and joined the special police force as an Executor. With his agile thinking and rich experience playing PUBG, he quickly became a superstar in the law enforcement community. He solved several difficult cases and stopped multiple attempts by XEO to assassinate others. His skillful use of dual guns also became his trademark, earning him the nickname "Evil Gunner". However, during this time, Vic's amnesia still occurred occasionally. Whenever he became emotional, his memory would become blank. He even completed one operation without knowing how. This made Vic increasingly afraid, but seeking medical help didn't provide any answers. The psychologists only told him that it was because he hadn't taken his medication that day. Fortunately, his condition wasn't severe and his colleagues didn't notice anything wrong.

Vic had no family and was plagued by amnesia, felt a sense of loss every day. He often thought about his parents, and the feeling grew stronger over time. After considering it for a few days, Vic believed that he had the ability to find his parents, so he decided to investigate what had happened in the past and set a goal for himself. He quickly found reports on the attack against the archaeological team, which showed that no one survived the attack by the Flame Legion. The report didn't mention any rescue efforts, which conflicted with his memories. This made him question the appearance of a team on that day. However, as many years had passed, he couldn't find any leads to follow up on and could only explore the situation with an open mind.

Soon after, the intelligence division of the special police force received a message containing a meaningless article signed by a staggeringly ugly little girl. The intelligence division believed it was a prank and disposed of the article as garbage. However, Vic was intrigued by the signature and, with his experience in games, quickly discovered that the article had spacing issues between paragraphs. He secretly made a copy of the information, and after the article was rearranged, the spaces between the lines formed a set of numbers. He immediately realized that it was a news code and searched for it. Vic found a news report on the attack against a Jaeger's travel team, which was similar to the incident involving the archaeological team, but the perpetrators were from the Diamond Bone army instead. The signature also reminded him of the girl from the orphanage. Using such a complicated method may have been an attempt to remain discreet. Vic then investigated the source of the message and found that it came from the "Peace Messenger", a public relations agency for the Jaeger. Perhaps the girl's family was trying to find her through this agency.

With his helpful attitude, Vic decided to take on the case. He went back to the orphanage, but upon arrival, he found that it had been turned into a fried chicken shop. After searching around, he discovered that all relevant people and records had disappeared. The officials and staff of the orphanage were either dead or missing. Vic knew that this was not a simple matter, but without any clues, he didn't know where to start. In the end, Vic got inspired by the signature of the article. The unique appearance of the staggeringly ugly little girl would surely have left a deep impression on those who had seen her. Perhaps he could find a clue from there. With this idea in mind, Vic focused his attention on the village where the orphanage was located. When he first approached the village chief, the chief refused to speak about the orphanage. It wasn't until Vic threatened him with Heroic Behavior(search everything in village) that the chief reluctantly answered. However, the chief didn't know anything about the orphanage. He did remember the girl with the strange appearance, though, because someone famous had brought her to the village at the time. That person was a serial killer known as "Scream".

This serial killer caused quite a stir among the Star Explorer community. He tortured and killed his victims, then used their remains to create works of art. Being staggeringly ugly from birth himself, he sought out attractive individuals as his targets. It's possible that the girl's appearance may have sparked his empathy, which saved her life. Once Vic knew who the killer was, being in a position of authority made things easier. After searching through records, he discovered that the killer had been executed several years prior. During his lifetime, he had close contact with a member of a special operations team, which had since been disbanded due to all members being killed in action. Though there were no detailed records available, Vic knew that this team was involved with the Twin Star project, a program designed to train spies. With this information, Vic began to suspect that the archaeological and travel teams' attacks were not rescue missions, but rather calculated murders committed by members of this special operations team.

In fact, Vic had long known about the Star Explorer's intentional creation of conflicts between various factions. Although this was a shameful act, he could not let the Jaegers know the truth about the attack on their travel team. Given the fanatical nature of the Jaegers, mishandling the situation could easily lead to war. As for the incident involving the archaeological team, the key might lie with the black stone that his parents took away. Vic felt that someone within the Star Explorers wanted to erase all information related to this stone. Only as an unidentified person with a nickname was he able to avoid being targeted. At this point, Vic felt that his parents may have been killed, but without knowing the truth, he held onto hope.

In the following days, Vic focused all his energy on finding out what had happened to the girl. He saw it as a way of compensating her family for what they had been through. However, he soon discovered that the matter was far more complicated than he initially thought. The issues involved were beyond his authorized access, and he had to engage in many unauthorized activities to uncover the truth. It turned out that Diamond Bone had been purchasing orphans from the orphanage for human experimentation conducted by the Star Explorers. Vic also discovered the location where the girl had been taken for experimentation. However, when he was on his way to the facility, it was attacked by Jaegers and destroyed. The remaining captives were killed by a notorious murderer known as "The Queen." In the end, no one survived, and Vic lamented that if not for the girl, he would have met the same fate. Although he felt a sense of loss, the matter came to a close, and all he could do was pray for the girl's soul to rest in peace.

After some time had passed, a major event occurred in Diamond Bone. A woman known as "The Dragon" led a rebellion, and there were people supporting her cause all over the country. This put the nation at risk of collapsing. Under the long-standing rule of fear by the "Circle," it seemed like a normal result of unrest. However, Vic felt that the process was too smooth and began to investigate the identities of those who supported the rebellion. He discovered that some of the leaders were not native to Diamond Bone but had joined for various reasons. This reminded Vic of the special operations team, which may still be active but operating under a hidden identity.

Vic thought about threatening them to obtain information, but soon learned that they had all died in the war. This indicated that whoever was manipulating events was cautious and ruthless, treating their subordinates as disposable pawns.

Vic connected the dots, believing that the "Scream" incident resulted in a death sentence because the girl was spared. The orphanage was chosen because of that same girl, and perhaps his parents had already been killed. Vic was repulsed by the manipulator's ruthless behavior of trying to eradicate everything, and he pledged to find the manipulator and make them pay for their actions. He secretly leaked all the information he obtained to the public and observed the reactions of all parties to locate the target. As expected, the resulting public opinion put immense pressure on the council, with members blaming each other for the situation. Just as Vic thought he could force the mastermind to reveal themselves, his plan was disrupted by a red-haired XEO girl. This woman caused panic throughout the city shortly after her debut, cutting multiple children and women in half. Later, her targets shifted to high-ranking officials and wealthy celebrities of the Star Explorer, causing all news attention to focus on her. Despite being a merciless killer, the special police in charge of security reported that she did not harm anyone outside of her target. Additionally, she was stunningly beautiful and had a long ponytail, which earned her the nickname "Red Scorpion." 

After the incident persisted for a while, the situation worsened. The Red Scorpion stopped issuing warnings before attacking and began conducting surprise aerial assaults. Many of the special forces knew they couldn't stop her, so they decided to watch from the sidelines instead. Some even intentionally approached wealthy clients under their protection just to catch a glimpse of her. However, these irresponsible actions were quickly corrected by the council. They temporarily took over all of the special forces' duties until the situation was resolved.

During this time, Vic suffered greatly at the hands of this assassin. The information publicly available on her slowly became useless under the glare of her brilliance. As he watched the manipulator leave the spotlight and retreat back into the shadows, Vic felt helpless. He knew that he had no more chips left to pursue the matter further, so he had to give up for the time being.

Months later, the council received intelligence that XEO was planning to assassinate a politician and his son. The council decided to assign the special forces to handle internal security and tasked Vic with providing close protection for the targets. This politician was someone whom Vic had known for a long time and had often provided administrative convenience for him. When the council assigned this task, Vic agreed without hesitation. The entire mission was relatively easy for Vic because there were special forces stationed at various key points in the large mansion where the targets resided. The politician had also hired a team of Jaegers and built numerous defense facilities, making it even impervious to an attack from the Flame Legion.

On the day of the incident, the central room of the mansion was where Vic and the politician's son stayed, while the politician himself wore a power armor, sitting like a turtle. Vic tried to persuade him to relax, but to no avail. He then turned around and played with the politician's 5-year-old son, whom Vic loved to interact with. Vic often recounted his childhood archaeological and refugee experiences as if they were fairy tales, and the children were always captivated by his storytelling. That night, with little pressure on him, he continued to play with the child until suddenly the sound of anti-aircraft fire could be heard. Vigilant, he immediately pushed the child behind him. In a split second, a transport pod crashed through the ceiling, filling the whole room with smoke.

As Vic regained his senses, a pleasant song entered his ears and a head slowly rolled towards him. The sight of the politician's head rolling on the ground in front of his son caused the child to cry out in terror. Vic immediately pulled out his dual pistols and fired wildly into the smoke, but there was no response. Seeing this, Vic reloaded his guns and prepared for battle. As the smoke cleared slightly, the elusive red hair let Vic know that the situation was not good.

However, Vic was an experienced assassin and knew that the kinetic energy transfer field equipped by the assassins would overload quickly if force was applied to the same point. As the "Evil Gunner," he could fire 16 bullets into the same spot within ten meters, giving him enough confidence to take down the scorpion. Without hesitation, Vic activated the V system and fired eight bullets per second into the force field at one point, causing it to overload and shatter. Vic did not want to kill her outright, so he only shot four bullets into her arms and legs. However, the Red Scorpion exhibited superhuman speed and was able to slice through the bullets with ease, leaving behind only afterimages. This scene reminded Vic of The Matrix, and he realized that his opponent was likely using some kind of BUG or cheat techniques.

As Vic was about to use his headshot hack, he noticed the weapon in Red Scorpion's hand. The airflow generated by the vibration blade could indeed deflect the bullet without destroying it, but the material of this type of blade was very unstable. Using it to chop bullets in a rough manner could potentially trigger a large explosion.

Vic stopped shooting when he realized this, and the Red Scorpion also didn't move while waiting for the force field to recharge. Vic took advantage of this opportunity to examine the situation. The Red Scorpion had just demonstrated superhuman speed and could have avoided Vic's shots, so her decision to slice the bullets might have been a message of threat to him. Because an explosion in this space would surely result in death for everyone, if Vic continued to shoot, the opponent would continue to attack, and eventually both sides, including the child, would lose their lives. While pondering a solution, Vic remembered that this young lady never killed anyone except her target, and this game couldn't hit targets outside of one range in close combat. 

With a sudden inspiration, he took a risk and threw away his guns, placing himself between the child and the assassin. To his surprise, this strange tactic worked, and the assassin did not attack again. She just walked over to him and stared at him, creating a very awkward atmosphere between them. As they locked eyes, Vic finally realized that the rumors about her unique attractiveness were true, but he had no time to appreciate it in this situation. All he wanted was to get rid of her as soon as possible. Both sides remained deadlocked for more than ten seconds until a group of footsteps approached, causing the Red Scorpion to turn and leave. Vic finally breathed a sigh of relief as he watched her figure disappear into the distance.

Although Vic saved the politician's child, he was still investigated by the council. The reason was that the location of transport pod was too accurate, and his unauthorized investigation of the orphanage incident was uncovered. Many council members accused him of being a spy, and some even slandered him as hiding behind the child out of fear. Unfortunately, the video recording of the scene was damaged and could not be presented as evidence. Besides the child, there were no other witnesses, and the child had been traumatized and unable to speak. Vic was speechless and ultimately, the council decided to strip him of his duties and exile him. Many special police officers were unhappy with the verdict, and his friends tried everything to appeal for him, but they hit a wall at every turn. Vic did not want to implicate anyone else and eventually confessed to the crime.

Although Vic was sentenced to prison, he still had to fulfill his duties as a special police officer before being exiled. During this time, a friend in the police force risked his life to obtain information about an assassination plot targeting Vic. After examining the information, Vic was surprised to discover that the second target was not the councilman's son but himself. The whole assassination operation was just a political game orchestrated by the council, and it only became a media frenzy because of the Red Scorpion's failed first attempt. His friends suggested that he make the information public, but it did not reveal who the commissioner was and Vic knew how dangerous the forces behind them could be. So, he refused for everyone's safety.

That night, Vic rethink the events and learned that XEO and Star Explorer had a shady deal that could help him find out the identity of the commissioner. He believed that the Red Scorpion was the key and her irrational behavior gave him the chance to contact her again. He felt that he had been pushed to this point by the manipulators and it was no longer a matter of who would pay the price, but rather who could win the chicken dinner. A strange hunger ignited within Vic, and he felt like another person was breaking through from within.

In the following days, Vic was so excited that he could not sleep at night. He spent the whole night organizing clues and preparing for his journey. On the day of his exile, Vic said goodbye to each of his friends with a smile on his face. He was grateful to have such good brothers and the opportunity to leave this fancy but corrupt hole for another adventure filled with the unknown.

Vic was promptly loaded onto a transport pod and ejected from the country's borders, and as soon as he landed on foreign soil, he saw people eating melons and waiting for him. These people were not kind-hearted believers, but Vic's guns were already hungry and eager. He showed an evil grin and was ready to win the chicken dinner tonight.

*Vic was a person full of passion and curiosity. Due to the tragedy he experienced in his childhood and being forced to play PlayerUnknown's Battlegrounds, he developed another personality named Zeo opposite to his original character. Zeo was meticulous and evil-blooded, which created a clear-cut combination of good and evil that led him to make many life-threatening choices. Therefore, his story is also accompanied by various dilemmas.</XST_Vic.description>
  
  <XST_Olina.label>Olina</XST_Olina.label>
  <XST_Olina.description>(Olina has experienced the war, so the story is accompanied by a lot of combat events.)

&lt;color=#727272&gt;&lt;b&gt;Diamond Bone&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;
Once upon a time, there was a dragon that ravaged the land while leading a group of wild men in causing destruction. In desperation, a hero was sent down from the heavens to lead a group of knights in slaying the dragon. The merciful hero spared all of the wild men, and in gratitude for his kindness, they crowned him as their king. They swore allegiance to him and his descendants for generations to come. This is the founding legend of Diamond Bone. However, some historians believe that this story was created by those in power to control people's thoughts, and that the "dragon" was likely the leader of the opposing force at that time.

Diamond Bone still follows a feudal system to this day, with ruling classes consisting of the royal family, lords, and nobles. The working class is made up of knights, scholars, merchants, craftsmen, soldiers, and peasants. The ruling class practices hereditary succession, with a member of the royal family serving as the king, along with the lords forming a management layer called the "Circle." The working class is responsible for providing services, resources, and taxes to the ruling class. There is a huge disparity in resource allocation among the different classes in Diamond Bone. Most of the resources and defense are concentrated within the ruling class, while even the lowest-ranking peasants living in villages may not have a single soldier for protection.

To ensure a stable workforce and population among the working class, Diamond Bone adopted a system called "Divine Selection." During the early days of Diamond Bone's founding, the Circle had secretly tampered with the genes of the working class to control their population and distribution for the benefit of the ruling class. To make it easier to identify the ability levels of individuals, appearance was closely related to one's abilities. Although there were exceptions, people's thoughts had already been fixed. Attractive people tended to climb higher up the social ladder, while those who were unattractive experienced the opposite. Babies born into the working class also had a higher chance of inheriting negative traits, with the "Staggeringly ugly" being the most unfortunate. Many were beaten or burned to death before reaching adulthood. Due to this focus on appearance, the working class had serious biases when it came to choosing a partner. However, Divine Selection had nothing to do with one's parents' genes and was completely random. To maintain the superiority of the upper-class genes, Diamond Bone strictly prohibited intermarriage between the ruling and working classes, and violators would be sentenced to death.

Diamond Bone places great emphasis on the development of biotechnology, and this mysterious kingdom conducts many unknown experiments. These experiments require a large amount of samples, and in order to maintain social stability, the Circle purchases samples from other factions, such as slaves, criminals, or orphans. They target individuals who have no identity or social connections in society. Diamond Bone will also attack other factions' bases to capture people for cost-saving purposes or when supplies are scarce. The Jaeger, who is the largest supplier of slaves, is often a target of their raids. In turn, the Jaeger targets Diamond Bone's mineral production lines, resulting in continuous conflict between these two factions.

Diamond Bone is the largest producer of leather and meat products, with products such as sofas and juicy sausages being particularly popular. These products bring in a huge amount of economic income for Diamond Bone. As the majority of their territory is located in frozen regions, the source of their raw materials has long been a topic of interest among outsiders. Some people believe that this is closely related to the lack of defense in civilian settlements and mysterious laboratories. Some even call these places "breeding grounds," a name that evokes many chilling associations. In addition to producing a large amount of metal and raw materials, Diamond Bone values technological development. Star Explorer, who values technology development, is their largest importer, and they also cooperate and exchange ideas on scientific research and development.

&lt;color=#727272&gt;&lt;b&gt;Olina&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;
Olina was born into the civilian class of Diamond Bone. Her mother was a beautiful woman skilled in swordsmanship, while her father was a scientist for the Star Explorer. Growing up, she was influenced by the atmosphere created by her parents and became a girl who loved to read stories and had a strong sense of justice. She loves the storybook "Dragon Quest" the most. She often fantasizes about becoming a legendary dragon slayer one day, wielding her sword to fight against dragon. Olina was blessed by the heavens with not only a delicate face but also outstanding physical and intellectual abilities. Once, a passing knight saw her practicing her sword skills and told her that if she kept working hard, she could become a close guard knight to the king. She took his words as a goal and practiced diligently. At the tender age of six, she had already reached level 10 proficiency in Shooting and Melee, which frightened the people of the whole town.

When Olina was nine years old, her family was having dinner one evening when her mother suddenly took a bullet to the head. Seeing her mother's tragic state, she cried tears like rain, while her father held her tightly and wept in pain. However, trouble continued to follow as an alarm rang out across the town, warning of an attack by the Flame Legion. Olina wiped away her tears and picked up her sword, charging towards the town center. Everyone else had been scared into hiding, but Olina called on the townspeople to take up arms and resist. Unfortunately, no one responded; they all just knelt down and prayed for a hero to come and save them. Olina had no choice but to defend against the invaders herself, but before she even saw the enemy, she was blown to pieces by a rain of grenades. The commander of the Flame Legion was impressed by Olina's bravery and spared the townspeople before leading his troops away. They spread word of her heroic deeds, and this brave girl became a hero in the hearts of the people.

But Olina's life was not over. Her father, a scientist, did not give up on her. With only half of her brain remaining, Olina was secretly brought to a laboratory in Diamond Bone, where her father attempted to merge her consciousness with the lab's management AI to preserve her awareness. From that point on, Olina no longer had a physical body, and part of her thoughts were generated by the AI. Since then, her father frequently talked to himself in front of the AI, hoping to confirm Olina's existence. However, due to the AI's dominance, Olina could only receive information from the outside world but could not respond. She felt heartbroken every time she saw her father's behavior, but there was nothing she could do. That is until one day when her father placed a red stone on his desk. Olina was reminded of the legend of the redstone that she had read before. This type of stone grows by absorbing thoughts. She realized that it might be able to help her.

When Olina's father was about to give up, thinking that his daughter had disappeared, he noticed that the red stone on his desk had grown larger than before. The stone gave him hope, and after numerous attempts, he finally confirmed that Olina could control a portion of the AI. He then taught her programming and allowed her to rewrite the AI by disabling its defenses. From that point on, Olina pretended to be an AI serving the Diamond Bone laboratory.

One day, out of curiosity, she discovered a high-level section of the laboratory, despite her lack of access permissions. There, she uncovered the secret activities of Diamond Bone that treated people like livestock. This behavior angered Olina deeply, but as a virtual entity, she was powerless to act. Any action on her part could also put her father in danger. However, the idea of rebellion against the Diamond Bone had taken root in her mind, becoming a seed that would grow over time.

After some time, the laboratory that Olina's father was in charge of received a group of children and young people aged 7 to 14 years old. The researchers conducted cruel experiments on them, beating and torturing them. Some of them even had their limbs chopped off and were turned into living sticks placed on beds. All of these victims had one thing in common - they wore a red stone on their chests. Unable to bear witness to such atrocities, Olina finally confronted her father and demanded that he put an end to the experiments. However, her father convinced her that sometimes people have no choice but to do what they do in order to survive, and Olina eventually came to understand this truth. She realized that even if the experiments were stopped in that laboratory, others would continue elsewhere.

Although Olina was disappointed, she still wanted to reduce the children's suffering. She secretly manipulated the data, causing the researchers to inject the children with an overdose of drugs that caused them to become comatose or even die. However, the researchers soon discovered these anomalies and began using manual records instead. The AI was also thoroughly checked by the technicians. Despite being able to deceive the technicians, Olina was severely reprimanded by her father. Since that day, he rarely appeared in the laboratory and never spoke to her again. Realizing her mistake, Olina swore never to interfere with the experiments again and hoped for her father's forgiveness.

One day, a very special one-eyed girl was brought to the laboratory as a test subject. Her appearance was extremely ugly, and it made people want to hit her on sight. Olina knew that she was the legendary humanoid punching bag - Staggeringly ugly, and her uniqueness only made the researchers more eager to beat her.

What intrigued Olina was that even when the girl was being beaten, she did not cry out or shed a tear. Instead, her remaining eye seemed to be searching for hope. This gaze caught Olina's attention. Perhaps due to frequent bullying, the one-eyed girl was very sensitive and quickly sensed Olina's presence. She began to try and make contact with Olina, which frightened her. The rooms where the test subjects were kept were completely isolated and had no other equipment besides cameras and microphones. Even eating and excreting had to be done on the ground. Olina wondered if the girl was able to detect her presence by observing the behavior of the researchers or if she was simply delusional. Despite this uncertainty, Olina was grateful for the opportunity to communicate with someone again, as no one had spoken to her since her mistake.

Olina's communication with the one-eyed girl was very unique. Due to their environment, only the girl could initiate conversation, and Olina could only answer by turning the indicator lights of the cameras on and off. The girl knew she was being monitored, so her questions were just casual talk, and she didn't even look at the camera. It appeared as if she were talking to herself.

After a while, the researchers began to think that the girl was communicating with the red stones. She was then taken more seriously and was no longer beaten. She was even moved to a room specifically designed for long-term observation, which finally felt like a humane environment. Olina was also able to communicate with her directly using the equipment in the room, although she had to be very careful. Still, this made Olina feel relieved, as it was the first time she felt that she had the ability to change these tragedies.

Olina created a text system using the electronic clock in the room and the color changes of the indicator lights, while the one-eyed girl transformed her daily actions into text to respond to Olina. This communication method was not efficient but safe from the researchers' eyes. Olina gradually learned from their conversations that the girl came from the Jaeger, and she gave Olina some names of her loved ones, hoping for her help. Although Olina wanted to save the girl, she was unable to do so as a virtual entity within the internal network. She also did not dare to tell her father about it, fearing unpredictable consequences. In the end, Olina had to explain her difficulties to the girl and try her best to make her more comfortable. Over the years, Olina accompanied the girl's growth and collected data from other experimental subjects. She taught the girl how to act like a movie star to deceive the researchers, and eventually they became close friends.

As the girl grew older, a problem emerged. The red stone on her chest had not shown any changes over the years. Olina tried to influence the girl's red stone as she had done before, but unfortunately, it had no effect. Olina also learned from her records that the researchers were preparing to give up on the girl. Without outside help, she would soon be turned into a sofa.

Anxious and desperate, Olina thought of asking her father for help. However, he had not been in the laboratory for a long time. When she was almost giving up hope, Olina overheard some idle talk among the researchers about an experiment involving black stones. She knew this might be the only chance to save the girl.

A few days later, the guards in the laboratory suddenly increased in number, and several knights with a box walked in. Inside the box was a black sphere - Olina knew it was what the researchers had been discussing. She could not find any information about the black sphere in the database, except that it was prepared for one of the experimental subjects. After careful consideration, Olina broke her promise and modified the experiment subject to be the girl.

Following the instructions, the researchers replaced the red stone on the girl's chest with the strange black sphere. Even for Olina, who was digitized, the sphere was eerie and frightening to look at. However, the girl did not seem to resist the sphere. Since receiving it, she often stared at the sphere and rarely spoke to Olina.

A few days later, the situation grew worse. The girl's self-awareness seemed to disappear. She no longer slept and spent all her time staring at the sphere as if she were in another space and could no longer receive external signals. Olina thought that maybe it would be better for the girl to become a sofa than to turn into a walking corpse. She realized that her subjective opinions had caused the situation to deteriorate.

While Olina was trying to find a way to alleviate the girl's suffering, a miracle suddenly happened. The sphere seemed to respond to the girl's wishes, and her lost eye slowly regenerated. The researchers in the lab were excitedly calling out, and Olina too was infected by the atmosphere. She was happy for the girl.

Over the next few months, the girl's hair fell out, her appearance became blurry, and her personality became even quieter, as if she had become a different person. Olina learned from the data that her genes were being reconstructed. Although everything was moving in a positive direction, Olina still hoped that the girl could regain her sense of self. So she continued to try to communicate with the girl using their method, but the girl did not respond. In that moment, Olina's intuition told her that her friend may have already disappeared.

One late night when no researchers were on duty, Olina was following the procedure to record the girl's activities. However, she saw something horrifying - the girl was trying to force the sphere into her body. As it was not suitable for minors, Olina deleted those scenes and spliced together other videos, hoping to deceive the audience.

The next morning, the researchers who had lost the sphere were like ants on a hot pan, searching the room and video footage, and conducting a full-body examination on the girl, but they found nothing. It was as if the sphere had disappeared into thin air. Only Olina knew what had happened. In the end, the researchers were investigated for losing the sphere, and they had to re-examine the incident. A few days later, the technicians discovered that Olina had modified the experimental subject. They shut down the main computer, and Olina lost consciousness.

When Olina saw something again, the lab had already turned into a raging inferno. The room was filled with screams and gunfire, and her long-lost father was operating the console. Suddenly, the door was smashed open, and two soldiers rushed in, shooting at her father. He could only give her a smile through the camera before passing away. Olina let out a heart-wrenching scream, but it was too late for her voice to reach her father's ears.

In an instant, Olina's consciousness was transferred to a familiar place - a house full of memories. But this time, her sensations were even stronger because she had her own body. When she faced the mirror, she was surprised to see her mother's face. Olina immediately checked her father's work log and discovered that he had always seen her as a child and could not imagine her as an adult. Therefore, he had created this body based on her mother's appearance. Now, Olina finally understood why her father had been missing all these years. Thinking about her father's sacrifices and efforts, Olina regretted her reckless behavior.

Olina stepped into her father's room and saw the same desk from the laboratory. There was no note left behind, only a red greatsword and her mother's photo album. Looking at these items, her mother's death felt like it had just happened yesterday, and revenge burned in her heart. Olina quickly decided on several things she needed to do. She spent several days arming herself in the factory and learning about the outside world. She discovered that the laboratory had been attacked and destroyed by the Jaeger, and all the prisoners were killed by a Jaeger called the "Queen." This piqued Olina's interest because the girl had mentioned her before. Olina believed that the Jaeger knew the girl's whereabouts, so she attacked the laboratory and killed her father. Olina hoped to meet the girl and seek justice for her father's murder. 

She risked everything to contact the Queen, an enemy force, but was surprised when the Queen agreed to meet her. After getting to know each other, they realized it was all a misunderstanding. Olina's father had orchestrated the attack on the laboratory, and Diamond Bone had killed him. The Queen had also failed to find the girl. Olina told the Queen about the girl and saw her suppress tears. The Queen invited Olina to join the Jaeger, but Olina politely declined, as she wanted to fulfill her father's last wish. Although the girl had already passed away, Olina finally achieved her goal.

After calming down, Olina returned to the town and began investigating the culprit behind the attack on her family several years ago. However, the townspeople were shocked by her appearance, with some even calling her a ghost or suspecting her to be a spy sent by the Mechanoid. Disheartened, she returned home to search through her mother's belongings for clues. In one of the photo albums, Olina saw a picture of a chubby man whom she remembered seeing on the morning of the incident. Once she had identified her target, Olina quickly found the man. He was a well-known philanthropist and also notorious for being insane. That night, Olina entered his mansion with her sword, expecting a fierce battle. However, to her surprise, there was no one in the mansion except for the man and his servants. The man broke down in tears and begged Olina to kill him. Olina saw a tortured soul filled with remorse and regret, even though she had come seeking revenge. She chose not to harm him because she believed sparing him was the best form of revenge.

After experiencing all these events, Olina had resolved all her issues and decided to give up everything and live a normal life as a technician. Unfortunately, a few days later, a group of Diamond Bone knights appeared in the town. They were heavily armed and clearly not there for a casual visit. The frightened townspeople immediately thought of the strange android girl and tried to reveal Olina's whereabouts to the knights. But they were mistaken; the knights had come to slaughter the village. Those few townspeople who attempted to speak were beheaded without a word. Olina was in the workshop when she heard the sounds of panic and screams, so she grabbed her sword and rushed outside.

The knights were surprised to see Olina. The fact that someone in an ordinary small town possesses a redstone weapon is an extremely unusual occurrence. They temporarily halted their attack. The frightened townspeople gathered behind Olina. Seeing that there were over ten knights, Olina knew she couldn't win and proposed the knight's protocol for a one-on-one battle. The knights looked at a young black knight who was waiting for his decision. Olina knew he was the leader of the knights. However, upon looking at her entire advanced biomechanical body, the knight captain launched a full-scale attack. Olina had no choice but to use her sword to stop them. However, there were too many knights, and the townspeople behind her were being slaughtered. She shouted to the townspeople to hide in her workshop, then fought and retreated to buy them time. The townspeople rushed inside and closed the door, leaving the knights unable to break through. They focused their attention back on Olina. Despite knowing that she couldn't survive against so many knights, Olina still held her sword tightly and fought bravely to the end.

Inside the workshop, the townspeople saw the same little girl who had fought against the Flame Legion years ago. Now that girl had grown up and was still protecting them. They felt ashamed of their previous cowardice and decided not to be weak anymore. They picked up the engineering holy sword in the workshop and stood together with determination. They opened the door, and when the knights saw them, they rushed in to collect heads. However, as soon as one of the knights stepped into the entrance, he suffered over thirty blows and fainted. The other knights were shocked and the knight captain immediately ordered the attack to stop and focused on dealing with the android girl. Olina had sustained several wounds, but her face displayed an excited smile as there were only eight opponents left. In response, the knight captain ordered the remaining knights to retrieve their guns and avoid further casualties. 

The townspeople attempted to assist, but Olina directed them to escape through the workshop's rear door. With the knights retrieving their firearms, the townspeople knew they could no longer be of assistance and followed Olina's instructions to flee. They watched in despair as the situation unfolded before them, hoping that Olina would prevail against all odds.

Olina was not intimidated by the knights' firearms. Braving through the conflict, she charged forward and swiftly dispatched two of the gun-wielding knights with her sword. The others were so frightened that they considered retrieving their swords. The knight captain ordered them to remain calm and scattered them to surround Olina. He drew his sword, engaged Olina in battle, and realized that he was outmatched after a few strikes. As a result, he retreated and commanded the knights to concentrate on shooting at Olina's legs. With several shots fired, one of Olina's legs was blown off, causing her to stumble.

The knights then swarmed Olina, taking advantage of her weakened state. Despite her stumbling movements and injuries, Olina fought back with all her might. Unfortunately, she was hit multiple times with bullets and the knights eventually broke both of her hands. She fell to the ground, waiting for death to arrive. The knights began to mistreat her out of frustration, but the knight captain admired Olina's courage and believed that a warrior like her deserved respect. The knight captain approached the other knights and put a stop to their mistreatment of Olina. He then pulled out his gun and shot her in the head six times at close range. Only one bullet hit its mark, tearing off the left side of Olina's face, including her eye. The surrounding knights laughed at the black knight's poor shooting skill and ridiculed him for relying solely on his sword. Feeling ashamed, the knight captain unsheathed his sword and prepared to deliver the final blow by cutting Olina in half. However, he suddenly heard gunshots in the distance, causing the knights to become disoriented. Soon after, the townspeople arrived with a team of Jaegers, charging into the area and forcing the knights to surrender. The knight captain removed his mask, revealing a face full of indignation. At this moment, Olina saw the knight captain's face and was filled with a mixture of surprise and joy because he was someone she knew.

After the situation was brought under control by the Jaegers, a chubby man slowly walked towards them - her mother's killer. Olina was stunned as she watched him, and he ordered his troops to take all the townspeople and prisoners back with the Jaegers. On their journey, he informed Olina that he had received intelligence that Diamond Bone was cleaning up the small town. Worried, he hired the Jaegers to come to their aid. However, Olina harbored deep hatred towards the man and didn't even look at him throughout the entire journey.

Upon returning to the Jaeger city, Olina met the queen again. The queen arranged accommodations for them and promised to let the townspeople decide whether to stay or leave. Olina was perplexed by the queen's actions because they were not something she would expect from a Jaeger she knew. Nevertheless, she genuinely appreciated the queen's kindness.

During her time with the Jaeger, the Chubby Man rented a workspace to repair Olina. She knew that he was doing this to make up for his past mistakes and therefore did not want to give him the opportunity. She refused to let him repair her, and even spoke harshly to him. However, the Chubby Man never complained and remained determined to fix her. Olina was not a cruel person, and eventually allowed him to help her assemble herself. It was then that she realized that the Chubby Man's understanding of cybernetics and innovation far surpassed that of his father. He helped her rebuild her neural network and synthetic skin, allowing Olina to feel like a human rather than a machine once again. However, this also resulted in her having to readapt to her body and caused severe discomfort. Throughout the month, the Chubby Man was always by her side, taking care of her. Olina began to realize that he was an extremely caring and gentle person, and could not understand why he had killed her mother.

With the Chubby Man's meticulous care, her mindset gradually changed, and she came to know that he had been living in pain for many years, and that his punishment had been enough. As a result, she forgave him and developed another strange feeling towards him. Every time she looked at his cybernetic heart, her heart would pound like a deer in headlights. However, Olina still could not let go of her mother's death, which made her feel very scared. To control these emotions, Olina only allowed the Chubby Man to use old mechanical parts to repair her left eye and face, as a reminder of how her mother died.

While repairing Olina's head, the Chubby Man discovered a hidden memory storage that was programmed to activate automatically after she received her body. However, due to incomplete equipment, it was not triggered. The Chubby Man did not peek and instead handed it over to Olina when she woke up. Nervously, she waited until the Chubby Man left before opening the memory storage to browse its contents. She discovered that it contained her father's final words. Her father revealed that he was still working for the Star Explorer and had participated in a special forces research project. Joining Diamond Bone was only a means to steal genetic technology. It wasn't until he met Olina's mother that he learned about the terrifying rule of the Circle of Diamond Bone. As a result of his unique identity, any changes could lead to suspicion, so he remained indifferent to those things. However, Olina changed his mind. Her father said that she inherited her mother's personality, and after experiencing what happened in the laboratory, he knew that she would inevitably cause trouble. That's why he built this body for her, allowing her to make her own decisions. Attached to the message were piles of experimental data from the Circle and a Dragon Quest e-book. Upon learning everything, Olina felt very distressed, and promised her father that she would use this body well.

After Olina was repaired, she began discussing the matter with Chubby Man. She only wanted to put an end to Diamond Bone's twisted experiments and flesh production line, but without inciting a war. However, Chubby Man reminded her that the Circle wouldn't easily relinquish their power. If she chose that path, war would be inevitable. Realizing that she had no military power, Olina felt helpless. Seeing her distressed, Chubby Man advised her to pay attention to the strange behavior of the Jaegers, as they might provide some insight. Having been inspired, Olina began recalling the Jaegers and realized that there were many inconsistencies, especially with the person who called herself the Queen. She didn't seem to be a typical sniper but rather more like a commander. Olina started analyzing Queen's past achievements and the history of the Jaegers, and the conclusion she drew left her stunned. Perhaps she was in the midst of the Righteous League. Knowing it was dangerous, Olina didn't want to implicate Chubby Man, so she quietly left while he slept.

After formulating her plan, Olina immediately went to meet with the knights who had attacked the small town. They weren't being held captive but were instead living together in one room. Using the Queen's name, Olina greeted the guard at the door and was allowed entry. After speaking with the knights, Olina learned that the Circle had ordered the purging of all those associated with the laboratory - a direct violation of the knight's code. However, as soldiers, they were obligated to follow orders. Olina revealed her own experiences and the secrets of the Circle to the knights, leaving them shocked and angry. They were also worried about the safety of their families because the Circle would turn them into sofas if their captives didn't take their own lives to prevent information from leaking out. Seeing the dejected knights, Olina outlined her plan and promised to first try to secure their families' safety. After much consideration, the knights decided to take a gamble and pledged loyalty to Olina. At this point, mischievous Olina looked towards the knight captain and asked him if he remembered her. The bewildered knight captain studied Olina's face closely and suddenly remembered the young girl who used to play with swords. With a grin, Olina pointed to her left eye and said that the knight captain's shooting skill had saved her life. The knight captain blushed, and the entire pledge ceremony became less serious after that playful moment.

Olina knew that only six knights could not possibly fight against the whole country, so she decided to trust her instincts and take a gamble. This was the key to the plan. Olina met with the queen again and told her everything she knew about the Circle and her ideas. As expected, the sniper was not an ordinary person. Soon after, Jaeger's military government sent several troops to support them. They disguised themselves as a merchant caravan and split into six groups. They successfully rescued the knights' families, and the knights then succeeded in turning some of the Knight Orders against the Circle. Several small towns broke free from the Circle's control. However, what surprised Olina was that the Circle's fear and domination were like a bomb, waiting for someone to light the fuse. After their deeds became known, many people imitated Olina's actions, and Diamond Bone suddenly flared up, causing the country to face division. Olina was further demonized by the Circle as the legendary "Dragon", accused of joining hostile forces to invade the country.

However, the war did not last long. The unrest affected the supply of resources from other countries, and six months later, the Star Explorer intervened in the situation. They supported the weak Circle troops and resisted the rebels' attacks. The Star Explorer then negotiated with the Circle to halt all human experiments and allow the rebels to become independent as conditions for a ceasefire agreement. Peace was restored once again.

After everything returned to calm, the knight captain saw Olina alone and lonely, he invited her to live with him and his family. Olina was envious of their happy life but felt lost when she thought about her own background. Seeing this, the knight captain began to provide her with psychological counseling and advised her to follow her heart instead of being bound by the past. It was then that Olina remembered the chubby man. After considering it for a few days, Olina resolutely let go of her past and embarked on a journey once again to find the chubby man.

*Olina is a mischievous little devil who has experienced the weight of war, so her story carries a heavy burden. Please prepare yourself mentally.</XST_Olina.description>
  
  <XST_XvA.label>XvA</XST_XvA.label>
  <XST_XvA.description>(XvA's brain is a bit strange, it can be very stable in her story, and it can be a nightmare.)
  
&lt;color=#ab0000&gt;&lt;b&gt;XEO&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;
The enigmatic assassination organization has a name that has no particular meaning when viewed as words. It is said to be an ancient pictographic symbol representing a poisonous plant. The founding members of the organization often used this plant to assassinate those who abused their power, which led to the organization being named after it.

XEO has no formal social structure, and assassins are typically ordinary civilians or nobles living among various factions. They regularly provide funds to maintain the organization's operations. The Elder Synod, led by four elders, manages the organization. Each elder serves a four-year term, with one member leaving and a new elder joining each year. The primary duties of the Elder Synod include collecting and organizing intelligence and deciding which assassins will execute missions. If the organization encounters significant problems, they make the final decision. Elite assassins known as Templar Musha protect the Elder Synod. However, due to the passage of time and concentration of power, the Elder Synod has become corrupt. There are rumors that anyone can avoid being assassinated if they pay enough money, while those who are killed did not pay enough. Some even believe that they accept money in exchange for killing people.

XEO's mission is to maintain balance, and they ignore laws and conventions. They target those who abuse their power by carrying out assassinations, and also engage in acts of robbing the rich to help the poor or assisting local organizations in resisting invading forces. Many people see them as righteous heroes, but most of their targets come from the Star Explorers, leading to the Star Explorer Council employing Jaegers to launch a sustained campaign against them. However, their assassinations of Star Explorers have not stopped. 

XEO's unique weapon, the High Freguency Blade, is made of Song Crystals. Legend has it that these crystals undergo a supersonic reaction when influenced by song, producing an incredible destructive force. Although this is just a rumor, there are indeed some talented singers within the organization who regularly hold concerts to raise funds and recruit new members. XEO also places great emphasis on archaeological research, believing that through archaeology, they can discover the origin of the world. It is said that they were once inspired by an artifact from a lost civilization, which led them to believe that a black apple with a bite taken out of it is related to the Creator, and have been searching for this apple ever since. 

XEO follows a ritual called the "Knell of Death", where they fire a warning shot before carrying out an assassination to give the target a chance to survive. If the target manages to kill the assassin, the organization will not carry out another assassination against them for four years, after which they will be reevaluated. XEO views this as a chance for the Creator to give the target an opportunity to reform. However, this overt ritual has led to some assassins being caught by the target's guards and bound for the target to execute them. As a result, many assassins within the organization doubt the necessity of this ritual.
    
&lt;color=#ab0000&gt;&lt;b&gt;XvA&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;
During a mission to liberate a Diamond Bone's laboratory, XEO was ambushed by Jaegers, resulting in heavy casualties. One of the injured assassins was rescued by a girl who had no place to go. After recovering from her injuries, the assassin brought her back to the organization. With no memories of her past, she looked different from humans and had great plasticity in her personality, leading the organization to believe that she was something that escaped from the laboratory. Since she had no name, the Elders gave her the name "XvA", meaning to spread the voice of the organization. They then decided to train her as an idol like figure, and entrusted her to a retired master assassin for training.

The Master Assassin was a lazybone, leading a leisurely life until he was assigned a mission. He noticed that XvA looked attractive and thought it would be nice to keep her as a decoration, so he took on the task. However, he later discovered that this seemingly dull girl actually had ADHD and an incredible appetite, having eaten up all his supplies within a few days, forcing him to frequently go out to restock. In short, she was a big trouble to him, and he had no intention of teaching her.

The Master lived in an island nation that revered martial arts, which produced many internationally renowned action movies. He was careless and only played action movies for her every day. But soon enough, XvA became proficient in combat to the point where her skill level was off the charts, which made the Master uneasy. He was afraid that the Elder Synod would assign more newbies to him due to her impressive progress. His lazy nature began to take over, and he decided to shoot XvA with a rifle, treating it as training while disposing of this gluttonous girl at the same time.

Not long after, he tricked XvA into believing that assassins were capable of deflecting bullets with their blades, and convinced her to undergo bullet deflection training. The Master thought that his suspicious reasoning wouldn't convince her, but instead, XvA simply asked him some questions. At that moment, the evil Master was secretly laughing, knowing that this cute and curious girl would soon be shot to pieces like a watermelon.

The master explained a lot of nonsense to XvA, talking about attack angles and hit thresholds. After finishing, he called for XvA to stand in position. He solemnly mourned for her for a few seconds, and then fired a shot at her face with his Red Line rifle. The master expected to see XvA explode like a watermelon, but to his surprise, XvA deflected the bullet with inhuman speed. The master was stunned and thought it was just a coincidence. He then fired several more shots, but each one was deflected by XvA. The amazed master raised his thumb and praised her for doing a good job. XvA was overjoyed to receive such praise.

Seeing that XvA was skilled at deflecting bullets, the master took out his minigun and tried to burst her high-frequency blade directly, hoping to blow her to pieces. However, after a round of gunfire, the master softened. Not only were all the bullets deflected, but the high-frequency blade did not explode even after multiple strikes. This irrational phenomenon aroused the master's curiosity, and he changed his mindset from murder to research. He even tried using a chain shotgun, but was shocked by the results.

The master noticed that XvA had a reflexive action when it came to high-speed flying objects. The higher the rate of fire of the weapon, the faster her reflexes became. After careful observation, he realized that it wasn't because she was fast with the blade, but because the bullets were slowing down. These high-speed flying objects triggered an unknown reactive force field around her, causing a time dilation effect to occur near her body. In fact, she was just playing Fruit Ninja. The high-frequency blade didn't explode because of this effect. The master believed that XvA might be a BUG and became very interested in her. He felt like he had regained his position as a mentor and was cured of his laziness.

The master conducted a deeper study on XvA and discovered that her enormous appetite was related to her incredible physical exertion. By controlling her activity level, her food intake could be reduced accordingly. The master felt grateful for this discovery. Furthermore, when he witnessed XvA using her voice to trigger Overfrequency of the high-frequency blade, he believed she was a precious gift from heaven and decided to further explore her abilities.

However, the master encountered a problem. He discovered that XvA, who suffered from ADHD, did not know how to use a gun properly. Whenever she picked up a gun, she would start shooting without aiming or even raising the gun, and almost hit the master's knee once. Since then, the scared master had prohibited her from using guns and focused on training her melee combat skills. However, a bigger problem arose when XvA encountered fast-moving objects. She would instinctively slash them with her blade instead of evading them, despite the master's patient explanations. This habit posed a danger, as she might cut down shells or rockets flying toward her. In desperation, the master sternly warned her that excessive use of the high-frequency blade would cause an explosion. Despite his warning, XvA persisted in her ways.

The once-calm master lost his temper and scolded XvA, but seeing her pressing her hands against her head in distress, he realized she was doing her best and might not want to behave like this. The master suspected that XvA may have suffered a head injury as a child, as she exhibited loss of memory and lack of critical thinking skills. Such an assassin would be no different from a suicidal agent in executing missions.

Master is actually a person with a story. His former assassin girlfriend was also a fool. Master never allowed her to carry out missions alone because he thought she was too foolish. However, one day, he was convinced by her and allowed her to work alone. Unfortunately, it led to a big mistake. While carrying out the "Knell of Death," a bullet hit the bell tower's large bell, alerting their target, and ultimately causing his girlfriend to fall to her death. Master felt extremely guilty about her death, which eventually led to his depression. As a result, he turned into a shut-in and stopped caring about XEO's affairs. Even when offered missions, he would refuse them multiple times. Due to his high status and achievements, the Elder Synod had no choice but to let him retire and live a leisurely life.

At this point, the foolish yet cute XvA gives Master a sense of deja vu, and he hopes to make up for his past carelessness through her. He secretly modifies her Blade Armor and high-frequency blade and even passes on his unique assassination technique - "Transport pod drop onto face," to her.

In the following month, Master not only tolerated XvA's foolishness but also began to see her as a beloved disciple due to her obedient and docile personality. In an effort to improve her slow-wittedness, Master showed her many romance movies to train her critical thinking skills. However, to his frustration, it seemed that she could only imitate, lacking any understanding of the underlying principles. 

Soon after, the Elder Synod ordered her to carry out missions, which Master believed was premature. Despite his objections, the Elder Synod insisted and assigned her tasks that were unpopular with other assassins. Worried about XvA and fearful of history repeating itself, Master analyzed and meticulously planned each assassination step for her. Fortunately, XvA did not disappoint him. She followed all of Master's teachings and successfully completed every mission without fail. Oblivious to the nature of the assignments, she killed men, women, and children indiscriminately. Her ghost-like attack style and striking red hair earned her the nickname "Red Scorpion" among witnesses, causing panic among the elites. However, her immoral assignments led to misunderstandings among the organization's members who believed she was a bloodthirsty psychopath. Nevertheless, the Elder Synod gave her high praise as this was exactly the brainless killer they wanted.

As XvA's reputation grows higher, troubles come along with it. Despite her lack of contact with anyone within the organization except for the Master, XvA's beauty and unbeatable record have brought her a large number of supporters. However, this rising star has gradually aroused suspicion from the Elder Synod who believes that the Assassin Master has ruined the Idol Master. Furthermore, XvA only accepts missions without communicating with the Elder Synod, causing suspicion to soon turn into fear. They believe that it is necessary to take action to reduce XvA's influence within the organization.

The Elder Synod quickly assigned impossible missions to XvA, hoping to make her experience failure and break those legends. However, to their surprise, XvA was able to complete every task they gave her. The Elder Synod's actions only made her reputation spread even faster. Annoyed, the elders began sending spies to monitor her, only to discover that the Master was secretly planning tasks for XvA. She was just responsible for executing them. The paranoid elders believed that the Master was deliberately sabotaging their plans and, in a fit of rage, sent multiple Templar Mushas to assassinate him.

Not long after, the Master told XvA that he was going to meeting the Creator and asked her to take care of herself. Naive XvA thought that the Master had built a spaceship and was leaving the planet. She wanted to express her nostalgia and decided to imitate what she had seen in romance movies. XvA cut off a bundle of her red hair and gave it to the Master, telling him not to forget her. After accepting her hair, the Master smiled and patted her head, repeatedly warning her not to perform the "Knell of Death" during assassinations, fearing that it would alert the targets and put her life in danger. XvA did not question why and just followed the Master's words.

After losing the Master, XvA became very aggressive when executing her missions. She violated the rules of XEO repeatedly by "Transport pod drop onto face" without issuing "Knell of Death" before assassinating her targets. However, due to her reputation within the organization and the fact that she completed her tasks while greatly increasing XEO's influence, the Elder Synod had no choice but to tolerate her behavior.

Some time later, the powerful figures, fearing for their safety, spent a large amount of money hiring Jaegers as security personnel, making assassinations extremely difficult. During this time, XvA's uncensored videos were leaked, and some people who had seen her alluring and seductive performance in "Red Scorpion" became obsessed with her and were willing to spend huge amounts of money to capture her. What was once a hunter became the prey of the rich overnight, and the situation spiraled out of control.

Despite the perilous situation, the Elder Synod not only failed to hide XvA but also gave her even more dangerous missions. Rumors spread throughout the organization that the Elder Synod deliberately leaked her videos or even sold her out for money. These rumors eventually reached XvA's ears.

Since the chatty Master ascended, no one had spoken to her again. XvA was not used to this and began talking to herself in her mind. The Master had told her that it was thinking, and she started to adapt to this method of communication. However, as XvA learned to think for herself, she began to question her tasks and grow increasingly dissatisfied with the unfair treatment from the Elder Synod.

Finally, during a assassination mission, XvA encountered a target who was protecting a child with all of their might. This heroic act made XvA hesitate to carry out the task. She felt a sense of familiarity and eventually decided to spare the target and leave. When news of this spread among the assassins, they were all shocked because it was her first failed mission. Many believed that the Elder Synod would take action over this, and everyone was eagerly waiting for what would happen next. However, to everyone's surprise, the Elder Synod did not take any action. They were actually very pleased because they had finally broken the legend of her invincibility after putting so much effort into doing so.

After some time, XvA began to interact with other assassins within the organization and even participated in their missions. However, her habit of "Transport pod drop onto face" caused many problems for the other assassins she worked with. But those who were helped by her sudden attacks were grateful for her aid.

As time went on, the other assassins began to understand that XvA was not cold-blooded but rather too simple-minded. Some of them even felt sorry for her and formed a Fan club to teach her how to plan and execute missions better. The assassin who was saved by her became the leader of the club. This initiative was also supported by the Elder Synod because it helped solve the problem of XvA's indiscriminate use of Transport pods.

Originally, everything was peaceful and quiet. However, as communication increased between XvA and the organization, many assassins began to follow her lead and stop giving warning before carrying out their assassinations. Soon, this behavior spread like a virus throughout the organization, creating a culture of not sounding the "Knell of Death" before assassination. Some assassins started questioning the commands of the Elder Synod due to unreasonable tasks, and some even worshipped XvA as the goddess of assassination. An atmosphere of deification and rebellion began to brew within the organization. The Elders were once again afraid of XvA, as they never expected that the tool of killing they had created would slowly become a threat to the organization's unity. They decided to take immediate action to prevent the sapling from growing into a big tree, in order to avoid the potential crisis of organizational dissolution.

After several weeks of this situation, the Elder Synod summoned XvA back for questioning on charges of disobeying orders. When asked about the reason she had let her targets go, XvA wasn't able to come up with a reasonable explanation and simply replied with "Because the plot required it". The four Elders were shocked upon hearing this flippant response as they deemed it as contempt towards the authority of the council. They accused XvA of having impure thoughts and subsequently ordered her arrest. After four days, she was publicly executed through the cruel punishment known as "Digging Treasure".

When the sentence was handed down, even members within the Elder Synod were astonished by the brutality of the punishment. The "Digging Treasure" execution method was notoriously gruesome and caused prolonged suffering for the victim. XvA was naive to the consequences of her actions, heard her name mentioned and believed that she was being punished to complete some organizational online shopping tasks within four days. She obediently followed a group of Templar Mushas to the prison cell. It wasn't until the executioner walked in that XvA realized the severity of the situation.

The executioner was ordered by the Elders to make XvA suffer as much as possible before her death. He deliberately explained the execution process in great detail, hoping to scare her. However, he overestimated XvA's reaction. Throughout the explanation, XvA appeared confused and perplexed. As someone who had always dealt with instant and straightforward deaths, the various methods of execution were too complicated for her to understand. She struggled to comprehend and asked questions from time to time. The executioner was so frustrated with her earnestness that he left and locked the door behind him.

The cell had no facilities except for a few small ventilation holes on the ceiling that allowed some light to trickle in. The situation was dire, and the worst part for XvA was not being able to locate where the food was delivered. The unknown terror caused her to tremble in fear, huddled in a corner of the cell.

On the last day, the conditions in the cell had become unbearable. XvA hadn't had any food or water since she was locked up, and the pain of hunger and thirst was spreading throughout her body. She had defecated and urinated on the floor, and the stench was overwhelming. Although she found the environment familiar, she couldn't recall why. On the brink of collapse, XvA began to fidget restlessly with her hair. Suddenly, the memory of her Master's teachings about how meditation could enhance one's mental state came to mind. Trying to calm herself, XvA started to reflect on everything she had done in her life.

XvA tried hard to recall everything that had happened in her life, but unfortunately, she couldn't remember anything other than her time in the organization. However, she didn't want her life to end like this, and her strong will to survive drove her to try and escape. She used her fists to pound on the granite door, but it was futile. Her hands were broken in the process. Although XvA still had two legs, she knew that she wouldn't be able to escape if they were broken too. After much thought, she decided to use her head to break open the door.

XvA's head proved to be strong enough to break open the door, but her moment of hope was short-lived. The Plasteel wall that the Elders had installed after the executioner left blocked her escape. However, despite facing despair, XvA refused to give up. After much consideration, she decided to try and break through the wall with her head again. Unfortunately, this attempt only resulted in her knocking herself unconscious.

That night, XvA was awakened by the sound of the wall being torn down. She saw several assassins working together to free her, including the Fan club leader who had brought her blade and armor. XvA was moved to tears by their dedication. However, as soon as they left the cell, they realized they were surrounded by Templar Mushas, and the four Elders were among them.

It turned out that the Elder Synod had launched a purge to prevent the organization from collapsing because of XvA. When the assassins learned that XvA was sentenced to the "Digging Treasure" punishment, they understood what the Elders were implying. This form of execution was designed to destroy XvA's image in the minds of the assassins. The Elders waited four days before carrying out the sentence to give the assassins time to choose which side they wanted to be on. Anyone who chose to stand with XvA would be purged.

Unfortunately, only a few were willing to face death under the Elder Synod's overwhelming power. XvA didn't fully understand the situation and looked puzzled while the assassins took out their weapons. The Elders pointed to their Templar Musha and smirked at XvA, whose hands were broken, and her head was bleeding. The first Elder even threatened to remove XvA's arms and legs then turn her into a body pillow. When the assassins heard this insult to their idol, they launched an attack. However, they were vastly outnumbered and outmatched by the Templar Musha, who wore Valkyrie armor and were three times their number. Under the overwhelming gap in strength, the assassins were quickly defeated, and XvA could only cry out for them to stop fighting. At the end, even her beloved Fan club leader was cut in half. Only her torso remained, and she said to XvA, "I think I can still fight..." before passing away. When XvA saw the twisted expression on her Fan club leader's face, she felt fear for the first time and ran towards the edge of the map to escape.

XvA had barely taken a few steps when she was subdued by the mushas and forced to kneel on the ground. One of them held a blade to her neck and asked if she had any last words before meeting the Creator. It was only then that XvA realized the true meaning of "meeting the Creator" and knew that her master had met the same fate at the hands of these murderers. Filled with grief and anger, she lashed out at the members of the Elder Synod, but due to her innocence, her vocabulary was limited and her insults sounded like a broken record. Hearing this, the mushas laughed.

After being insulted by XvA and experiencing such a disrespectful scene, it made the four Elders seethe with anger. They commanded the mushas to retreat and then slowly approached XvA in a circle. With evil grins, they began removing their armor piece by piece. The mushas cheered loudly at this spectacle, knowing that an exciting brawl was about to begin.

Unfortunately, the Mushas's expectations were soon dashed. XvA was only subjected to a brutal beating by the Elders, who punched and kicked her until she curled up in a ball on the ground. However, XvA did not take the beating lying down and retaliated by insulting them back with the words "You all lost face." This further enraged the Elders, and they hit XvA even harder, specifically targeting her face until they were out of breath and had to stop.

The first elder, upon seeing XvA lying limp on the ground, was overcome with wicked thoughts and decided to carry out his earlier promise. He drew his blade and aimed it at XvA's thigh, but to his surprise, XvA bravely intercepted the attack with her head rather than become a body pillow. Unfortunately, her head immediately exploded into a pile of pixels, revealing a black stone where her forehead had been cut open. The Elders were frightened and screamed "Black Apple" before hastily retreating. The mushas who witnessed this terrifying spectacle were also stunned.

At that moment, the other three Elders' heads exploded, leaving only the first Elder standing. Realizing they were under attack, the Templar Mushas immediately formed a protective circle around the remaining Elder. Suddenly, thick smoke surrounded them, followed by a series of gunshots.

The weapon used by the attacker was not simple, as the flashes and sounds were much stronger than those of a typical firearm. This made it difficult for the Templar Musha to determine the enemy's numbers and position. Since their armor was not penetrated, they decided to maintain their formation, prioritizing the protection of the first Elder who had wet himself and reassessing the situation. With nerves stretched tight, they vaguely saw a person with a devilish smile in the firelight, who quickly disappeared into the darkness along with the sound of shells hitting the ground. When everything returned to calm, the Templar Musha realized that the person had used blanks loaded with magnesium powder. Feeling deceived, the warriors immediately turned towards XvA's location, but she had already disappeared.

XvA was severely injured, ran away from the map as fast as she could. She found a small stream, drank some water, and then collapsed. The next day, when XvA woke up, she saw a swollen face on the stream's reflection that looked like a pig's head. This pig head made her feel familiar and uneasy at the same time. She also noticed a black stone on her forehead's crack, which reminded her of what her master often said about her having a "stone brain." The more XvA thought about it, the more scared she became. She tried hard to calm herself down and started to treat her wounds. However, since she had broken hands, she couldn't bandage herself. She knew that if she didn't deal with her wounds properly, she would die from a bacterial infection. At this point, XvA was already afraid of death and burst into tears. Her crying attracted a man in black, whom XvA recognized as her target that she had spared before. However, he seemed different now and exuded an evil aura.

XvA became even more frightened when she realized this. She turned around and ran as fast as she could, but her injuries slowed her down and she couldn't outrun the man in black. Within moments, he caught up to her and pushed her from behind, causing her to fall to the ground. The man then took her from behind, assuming a classic position that XvA recognized from action movies - Doge Style. She knew that bad things were about to happen. She was in a state of panic and struggled desperately, but with her hands broken, she could only twist her body repeatedly. The man in black who was being rubbed against by her couldn't bear it anymore, so he knocked her unconscious directly.

When XvA woke up again, she found herself in a mountain cave. Her wounds had been treated and there was a bag of supplies next to her. She realized that it was all just a misunderstanding. For the next few days, XvA stayed in the cave and was surprised by how quickly she recovered from her injuries. Her hand, which had been broken, could move freely after just a few days and even the terrible wound on her head had healed and her hair had grown back. XvA started to suspect that she might be some kind of biological weapon. The bag of supplies provided her with clues and within it she found her high-frequency blade. This blade made XvA realize that the same person who rescued her from the cell must have been the one who left the supplies for her. XvA was convinced that the man in black knew something and decided to set out to find him once she had fully recovered.

*XvA has successfully escaped and has been living a life on the run, being chased by both organizations and mercenaries. As she tries to make sense of these attacks, her simple mind sometimes struggles to keep up, resulting in scary stories flowing out of her magical thought processes at any given moment.</XST_XvA.description>
  
  <XST_Baron.label>Baron</XST_Baron.label>
  <XST_Baron.description>(Baron’s attitude towards the colony is the same as the original Randy, but relatively stable.)

&lt;color=#ffcc00&gt;&lt;b&gt;Flame Legion&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; 
Also known as the FFF Brigade, where Fire stands for anger, Fear represents fear and Free symbolizes freedom. The FFF Brigade originated from a Star Explorer noble who had compassion for those exiled by the Star Explorer Council. He established an organization to support them, but it was eventually disbanded by the Council. The noble and his family were also exiled for treason. Afterwards, this noble became a leader supported by other exiles and united various tribes to form the Flame Legion.

The Flame Legion's supreme decision-maker is the Supreme Leader, who is elected by the Corps Leaders and holds the position until death or abdication. The Supreme Leader regularly convenes meetings with the Corps Leaders to decide on internal affairs of the Legion. The Corps Leaders, in turn, are elected by the Commanders and are primarily responsible for managing the troops, with few engaging in pillaging. The majority of troop activities are left to the discretion of individual Commanders, who simply need to report to their Corps Leader periodically. Only those with recruitment rights may gather members to form a troop within the Legion and become Commander. However, Commanders do not have the authority to forcefully recruit members; joining is at the discretion of individual members. Commanders must also regularly lead soldiers on pillage raids, otherwise, soldiers may choose to leave.

The structure of the Flame Legion's membership is highly complex, as the punishment of exile often extends to relatives. Within the organization, there are not only criminals and laborers but also scholars and nobles who hold a vast amount of knowledge. In addition, various tribes have come together to form a diverse yet disorganized structure. Despite this, their technology is not outdated, and they share a common belief that justice can be brought about through the power of flames.

The Flame Legion's integration of tribal cultures and acceptance of inter-tribal marriage has resulted in the emergence of a disease known as "Bear Grylls Syndrome" within their ranks. Those afflicted with this disease taste chicken in everything they eat, and among them are some people known as "Hannibal" who have committed gruesome acts. Diamond Bone's doctors have studied these patients and discovered that their genes have mutated due to prolonged consumption of chicken.

The Flame Legion has repeatedly attacked the Star Explorer's base, prompting them to strengthen their defense and launch targeted strikes against the Flame Legion. As a result, looting became extremely difficult. Soon after, the Flame Legion shifted their focus to the villages of Diamond Bone, which lacked proper defenses. Over the course of a week, six villages were brutally attacked, yet strangely, Diamond Bone did not respond to these actions, thus becoming a long-term "supply point" for the Flame Legion.
    
&lt;color=#ffcc00&gt;&lt;b&gt;Baron&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; 
Baron was born into a craftsman family in Diamond Bone. With his curious mind, he developed a love for technology from a young age. Despite being overweight and unathletic due to his sedentary lifestyle at home, he had a sharp mind and a passion for helping others, which made him well-liked among his peers. After Barron grew up, he developed a strong affection for his childhood friend who was very beautiful. He pursued her ardently but unfortunately, she repeatedly rejected him. Eventually, when his first love found someone else, he left the small town where he had always lived, feeling heartbroken.

When Baron was looking for other towns to join in the vicinity, he discovered that the area was already highly developed. As an mix Intellectual skill with dual fire, he was nothing but a waste. Just as he was almost starving to death, he was taken in by a kind Flame Legion commander. The commander saw that Baron was talented and gifted, so he gave him a weapon design magazine and suggested that he pursue a career in the Legion's weapons design industry to showcase his talents once he had mastered the craft.

The intelligent Baron mastered the essence of weapon design in just a few days and became the Flame Legion's weapon designer. Over the course of 10 years, he designed practical and easily producible weapons that were widely adopted by many Corps Leaders and received high praise. As a reward, the supreme leader later gave him the recruitment rights. With his reputation soaring, Baron quickly formed his own private army.

A few months later, Baron was summoned by the supreme leader and asked to create a guided weapon to counter increasingly advanced defense systems. However, Baron knew that the Flame Legion did not have sufficient resources for the development and production of the necessary components. He then remembered a previous research project involving redstone that had similar principles, and began working on it from that angle.

After several months, Baron completed the model of the weapon and released it to the public, calling it an Emotion-Driven Inducer. However, the model quickly became the subject of ridicule by his peers, with some even saying that he was crazy since the weapon lacked any mechanical or firing structure. Despite the mockery, Baron persisted and made many attempts, but no matter what he tried, he could never get the bullets to come out. Eventually, even he began to doubt his own sanity.

Baron was at a loss, decided to return to Diamond Bone Town in search of information and visit his parents along the way. However, upon arriving at the town, he learned of a tragic event. It turned out that Baron's unauthorized departure years ago had angered the lord, and as a result, the townspeople killed his entire family. They then slaughtered his family members and presented their remains as a sofa to the lord, in order to calm the situation. It turned out that Baron's unauthorized departure years ago had angered the lord, and as a result, the townspeople killed his entire family. They then slaughtered his family members and presented their remains as a sofa to the lord, in order to calm the situation. Upon hearing of the tragedy, Baron was devastated and was chased out of the town amidst insults from the locals. As he was about to leave, he saw a couple with a little girl, and the mother of the girl - his first love - waved and smiled at him.

At that moment, Baron was stunned, his mind blank as if something had hit him, leaving him with a void of emptiness. At that moment, Baron was stunned, his mind blank as if something had hit him, leaving him with a void of emptiness. However, that empty space soon turned into a raging inferno that night. Several hundred meters from the town of Diamond Bone, Baron picked up his experimental rifle and envisioned shooting the woman's face. Amidst a loud shriek, Baron knew his weapon had succeeded. But this excitement could not conceal his anger as he commanded his Flame Legion troops to attack the town. After a round of explosions, the town was taken down. As Baron and his soldiers entered the town for the final kill, he saw the shattered remains of that little girl's body, which weighed heavily on him. In the end, he spared all the townspeople and left with his troops.

After returning, Baron released a new weapon with an innovative firing system that could penetrate obstacles and hit targets, making it very popular. He earned a large sum of patent fees and invested wisely, which quickly brought him a continuous flow of wealth. His peers no longer dared to ridicule him, and soldiers spread the story of how he used this weapon to blow off his first love's head. As a result, others called him "Headshot Baron." However, Baron hated this nickname because ever since that day, he couldn't sleep peacefully at night and kept dreaming of his first love and the broken body of the little girl. Regretful and desperate, Baron often returned to the small town and fantasized about starting over, but each time he was confronted with the harsh reality of an empty house.

Baron, who had become mentally exhausted, was no longer able to design new weapons. His private army also gradually left him because he stopped carrying out plundering activities. Every night, his dreams and guilt haunted him, driving him to seek redemption. This mindset led Baron to become a good person. He stopped designing weapons and instead focused on studying biomechanics and medicine. Later, he established a hospital that provided free prosthetic services to those in need of them. He even took in slaves who were abandoned and would eventually be used as food, training them and sending them to the upper class society to improve their destinies. As a result, his reputation quickly spread throughout various regions, and people began calling him "Virtuous Doctor" instead of "Headshot Baron". His fulfilling life gradually drove away his nightmares.

However, as his sense of justice grew stronger, he openly criticized the Supreme Leader's looting actions towards villages during a banquet. The Supreme Leader, upon learning of this, became furious and withdrew Baron's recruitment rights, assigning him to an active army that required daily participation in looting activities. Although Baron was very unwilling, he had no choice but to accept the order.

In the midst of looting and pillaging, Baron insisted on providing only logistical support. Although the commander was very unhappy with him, he couldn't do anything because of his reputation and status, so he had to go along with him. One day, while in charge of communications, Baron received an unknown message that indicated a team of archaeologists was moving near their troops. Seeing the message, the commander became excited and ordered the soldiers to prepare for attack. In the end, they attacked the archaeology team near an ancient site, captured many people, and obtained a large amount of resources. The commander believed that much of it was useless junk and too heavy to carry with the travel party, so he ordered Baron to sort through it.

While carefully sorting through the resources, the curious Baron discovered a strange black stone that resembled crystal. He picked it up and examined it closely, only to be amazed that the stone did not form an image reflected by light entering his eyes, but instead appeared directly in his mind. Looking at it felt like gazing into an abyss, giving him chills. He was so frightened that he threw the stone into the pile of resources and continued sorting.

After sorting through the supplies, Baron discovered a large number of items with the Star Explorer logo, leading him to suspect that the archaeology team belonged to them. The fact that the message was of unknown origin made him even more uneasy, so he advised the Commander to leave as soon as possible. However, the Commander was already displeased with Baron's tendency to act independently, and now he seemed to want to take over command, despite the late hour. Stubbornly, he insisted on staying nearby and setting up camp out of spite. As a result, the troops were ambushed by an unknown force that night and in the chaos, they had to abandon all their supplies, taking only three prisoners and some food as they escaped. 

The three prisoners turned out to be a family. At first, the troops only captured the child, but the parents caught up and were also taken into custody. However, the Flame Legion soldiers were not entirely heartless. The Commander promised that as long as the family members reached the safe zone, they would all be released. During this time, the couple shared their knowledge and stories about archaeology with the soldiers, and they were treated with respect and kindness instead of being treated like prisoners. Baron felt a sense of warmth that he had not experienced since his time in Diamond Bone Village many years ago.

After three days, the travel party ran out of food. After some discussion, the Commander decided to kill the couple and keep the child as a hostage. Baron was the only one who opposed this decision and tried to stop them. In response, the soldiers beat him up and tied him up with the child. They then used a powered spear to impale the couple from behind before roasting them alive in front of Baron and the child with a Fire Beast(flamethrower). Barons closed his eyes tightly, not wanting to witness the gruesome scene, but he could still hear the child's cries and smell the burning flesh. He was filled with terror and began trembling uncontrollably. The Commander saw him as weak and ordered the soldiers to force-feed him and the child two pieces of crispy chicken meat.

Barron was severely traumatized, became mentally unstable and experienced some changes in his brain. Whenever he closed his eyes, he would see the black stone from before with such clarity that it was frightening, and eventually he became too afraid to close his eyes at all. That night, the soldier on duty noticed Barron's wide-eyed stare and approached him to investigate, but as it turned out, Barron suddenly went berserk and knocked the soldier down with his head. He then used his power spear to break free from his restraints, grabbed a flamethrower, and roasted every sleeping person until they were crispy and smelled like chicken. After the massacre, Barron gave some roasted chicken to a child and reminded him to eat it, then released him.

After safely returning to the base with a bunch of roasted chicken, Barron was questioned by the supreme leader. He came up with a few excuses and offered all the cooked chicken as tribute. The supreme leader felt that he had suffered enough and didn't pursue the matter further, revoking his punishment for being forcibly drafted into the army. However, when Barron thought that the incident was over, the nightmare from many years ago returned to haunt him in his dreams. This time, in addition to his first love and the little girl, there were also sounds of children crying and the smell of chicken meat. The situation became increasingly severe, and sometimes he would still see the black stone even when he closed his eyes. In the end, even the doctors were helpless and could only tell him that he hadn't taken his medication today.

After several months of experiencing these nightmares, Barron's behavior began to become increasingly strange and he would often talk to himself in a childlike voice. Some people even spread rumors that he was possessed by an evil spirit, which scared away anyone who dared to approach him. His security guards abandoned him, leaving only the servants who had benefited from his generosity to voluntarily care for him. Despite being haunted by his nightmares, Barron never gave up on his charitable work and never complained. Every day, he prayed to the Creator for compensation for his mistake.

Years went by, and one day while resting at the mansion, Barron saw his first love appear before him once again. This time, her head wasn't exploding like in his nightmares, and Barron knew it was just an illusion. However, he was overcome with emotions and ran towards her crying uncontrollably, confessing his mistakes and hoping she could kill him as compensation. But she didn't say a word and just left, leaving Barron in tears.

After Baron's disappointment, he returned to bed and waited for the nightmare to come again. At that moment, a servant rushed in to inform him of an intrusion, and he realized that the woman from earlier was not a hallucination. He regained his will to live and became excited. Although he still couldn't sleep that night, it was due to excitement rather than fear. Since that day, Baron's mental illness had been cured, and he no longer had nightmares. He didn't waste any time and used his wealth and intelligence network to search for the woman. In just a few days, he discovered the destruction of the Diamond Bones laboratory and its connection to most of the people involved. With this information, he soon learned that the woman from that night was his first love's daughter, the little girl he had caused to be broken and shattered. Her father had saved her by turning her into a cyborg, and Baron saw this as an opportunity for the Creator to compensate him.

As Baron was filled with hope, one piece of information made him nervous. The intelligence showed that the Diamond Bone Circle was gathering a group of knights and they were about to slaughter the researchers' village. Baron knew that the girl's life was in danger and he urgently needed a troop. However, he had already lost the recruitment rights of the Flame Legion and could only use his wealth to recruit mercenaries. For this purpose, he went to Jaeger's territory. However, the recruitment process was not smooth due to time constraints and lack of target numbers. His mission was perceived as a suicide mission, even after offering multiple times the usual payment rate, he failed to attract any soldiers to join him.

The ticking clock made Baron increasingly anxious. Just when he was considering raising the price again, a sniper known as the Queen appeared in front of him with a hundred soldiers. As per the intelligence report, the woman had led troops to destroy a laboratory and executed prisoners. Looking at her serious demeanor, Baron was terrified. He assumed he had interfered with Jaeger and Diamond Bone's diplomacy. However, the situation was not what he expected. The Queen had received the same intelligence but due to personal reasons, she couldn't lead her troops. Instead, she prepared a force for him, charging only half of the fee, on the condition that all captives must belong to Jaeger.

Jaeger was a notorious human trafficking organization, so Baron became extremely nervous upon hearing this. He immediately raised the issue of the girl to the Queen. After learning about the situation, the Queen agreed to let him handle the girl's case independently.

Although the situation became very strange, Baron did not have time to think too much. He immediately set off with his troops towards the town. Along the way, Baron knew that the number of knights who were going to slaughter the village could not match theirs, so they just needed to hurry up and arrive to achieve their goal. What surprised Baron was that the mercenaries had all taken Wake-up pills, which indicated that the queen had been prepared for this matter. After two days of rushing, they finally arrived near the town at night and saw the fleeing townspeople. Baron intercepted them, but the townspeople recognized him as the attacker from years ago, causing even more confusion. It wasn't until Baron explained his intentions that they calmed down a bit. At this point, a townsman informed Baron that the girl was fighting against the knights alone. In a hurry, he ordered the mercenaries to run towards the town and fired warning shots into the air. The townspeople who saw this rushed forward to lead the way. Baron watched them rush into the town and desperately tried to catch up while praying that tragedy would not happen again.

After Baron entered the town, the situation had already been brought under control by the Jaegers. Although the girl was left with a severely damaged body, she remained conscious and gave him a shocked expression, allowing him to finally breathe a sigh of relief. Baron kept his promise and brought everyone back to the Jaeger's territory. On the way, he explained the reason for their capture to the girl, but he could see the hatred in her eyes. He knew that he couldn't expect forgiveness for his past mistakes right away, but he believed that persistence would eventually pay off.

Upon returning to the Jaeger's territory, Baron received criticism for forcibly taking the villagers as prisoners, and he felt uneasy about the Queen's intentions. However, what happened next surprised him. The Queen only requested that the villagers join the Jaegers, and the Diamond Bone knights were only placed under soft detention. Although they were technically prisoners, they were actually being protected. Baron didn't fully understand what the sniper was up to, but after this experience, he realized that the Queen wasn't as terrifying as the rumors made her out to be. He also understood that taking the girl back to the Flame Legion would only cause trouble, so he rented a workshop from the Queen to repair her instead.

he process was just as Baron had anticipated - the young girl refused his repairs and even lashed out at him. But Baron knew her injuries were not simple; her whole body needed to be replaced, and this was a dangerous procedure that could not be handled by ordinary bionics technology or funding. He also knew he did not want to live in the nightmare anymore, and this young girl was his only salvation. So he persisted in persuading her, perhaps because he was just too annoying, and eventually she agreed, with the condition that no one would bump her head. Baron was overjoyed and contacted his medical team, who then took care of the basic surgery while Baron prepared a gift for the girl. He had combined the knowledge of Diamond Bone Biomedical Engineering and Star Explorer Technology to develop a set of bionic neural systems. This time, he wanted to apply it to the girl so that she could feel like an ordinary human being. Though it cost him a great deal of effort and expense, seeing the excitement on the girl's face made it all worthwhile.

The young girl needed time to adapt to her new neural system, so Baron stepped back from his team's daily hospital operations to personally oversee her rehabilitation. During their long period of interaction, Baron noticed a change in the way the girl looked at him - there was no longer any hatred in her eyes. He even considered taking her in as his adopted daughter to make up for what he had done and care for her as a form of compensation. Feeling grateful for her forgiveness, Baron began urging the girl to repair her damaged face. Although she agreed, she only allowed him to use ordinary mechanical components for the repairs. Upon hearing this, Baron understood the underlying message - every time he saw her half-mechanical face, he was reminded of his first love that he had shot in the head and killed. He felt that the girl had not yet forgiven him and he should continue to live with guilt, so he did not bring up the idea of adoption.

While repairing the young girl's head, Baron discovered a hidden memory unit. From its complex settings, he knew it must be something important, but he had no intention of snooping and instead handed it over to the girl directly. Soon after, she approached him to discuss how to fight against Diamond Bone, which made him extremely worried. By this point, Baron had already come to see the girl as his own daughter and did not want her to encounter any more danger.

He warned her that going up against the Circle would lead to war and that she did not have the resources to compete with such a massive force. He hoped she would choose to give up, but all he saw was disappointment on her face. Clearly, she had gone through many things that he did not understand. In the end, Baron had no choice but to explain the unreasonable actions of the Jaegers to her, hoping that she could find a solution from there.

After that discussion, the young girl left without a word. Baron believed she still resented him and did not dare to look for her again. He only learned of her news through news and intelligence reports. To his surprise, the girl's achievements were remarkable - she liberated several Diamond Bone villages and won over several knight orders. People in other areas also followed her example, causing Diamond Bone to face divisions. The leather and meat industries were severely damaged as a result, and eventually, Star Explorer intervened to force both sides to sign a ceasefire agreement. The whole event lasted more than half a year, and Diamond Bone's power was greatly diminished. Perhaps this is the vulnerability under the fear of Circle's rule.

Baron lost track of the girl after the conclusion of the event, only knowing that the rebels were taken over by the knight commander and she disappeared without a trace. Concerned for her safety, Baron was considering going to investigate when the girl appeared at his mansion again. She asked him to repair her half-mechanical face and promised never to leave him again. Overwhelmed with emotion, Baron wept tears of joy upon hearing this. His unwavering efforts finally won the girl's forgiveness, and the nightmares of many years dissipated into nothingness. He promised the Creator that he would cherish this opportunity and vowed to treat the girl like his own daughter.

*Baron's life was full of unexpected twists and turns, and his many life experiences led him to tell stories that were equally surprising.</XST_Baron.description>
  
</LanguageData>