<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

<!-- XvA's Note -->
  <BookDescription_XFNote.rulePack.rulesStrings>
        <li>desc->This note is filled with numerous children's doodles and moon runes, only understandable by those not particularly bright.</li>
  </BookDescription_XFNote.rulePack.rulesStrings>

<!-- King of Black Sea -->
  <BookDescription_XFKOP.rulePack.rulesStrings>
        <li>desc->A medieval serf committed poaching due to lack of food. The nobleman, in compensation for the loss, slaughtered his wife and children like livestock and sold them for money. The serf never thought that his master would treat them this way. He watched his family die miserably, and shortly after, he went insane. With his innate resilience and expert combat skills, he picked up a chainsaw and charged into the noble's mansion. He killed the guards in just a few strokes and then turned his gaze to the terrified nobles and their families...

"First blood, Double kill, Triple kill..." He only calmed down when there was no more sound in the house. He began searching for treasure and found a black gem in a safe. The smooth surface of the gem reflected the nobles' death throes. At that moment, the serf realized that power is nothing more than a projection of force. With absolute force, he would never stand under anyone's command again.

From that day on, he used the stolen wealth to devise a plan. Other slaves in the estate formed a new force under his leadership and started recruiting talented people. Within a few years, he befriended seven hunters and shared with them his grand vision of changing the pirates' world to bring peace and order - "Do you want to hunt chickens for the rest of your life, or do you want to change the world with me?" The seven hunters were ultimately moved by his words and determined to create a great cause with him.

From then on, the eight men kept striking scattered pirates and recruiting and educating them. The pirates also developed a sense of mission because of the group's spiritual support and devoured other pirates in the name of justice. Their team gradually grew under this pattern until it became too large to maintain, and problems emerged.

The serf knew that this operating mode would eventually come to an end as the number of pirates decreased. This was also the opportunity he had been waiting for. He awakened the pirates' nature by using survival as an excuse, and more than half of the pirates quickly became his private soldiers. The team changed from a justice army to a monster that devoured everything, and the serf became the Pirate King.

The organization gradually declined, and even pirates who did not take sides gradually joined the Pirate King because of their need for survival. Under the Pirate King's indulgence, they lost all conscience and burned, killed, and plundered everywhere. The terrifying power was devouring everything. Soon many towns and villages succumbed to this terrible force. The seven men saw that the world might go dark from this point on, so they united with those who had truly repented and planned to assassinate the Pirate King.

That night, the seven men launched a surprise attack from within with their troops and stormed into the Pirate King's hall. The Pirate King, wearing golden armor and wielding a chainsaw, cowered among his guards, obviously frightened because he never thought that the seven would dare to betray him. His armed forces, which he had always been proud of, were defeated by their unity and determination. The Pirate King tried to quell their morale by proposing to solve the dilemma through a one-on-one fight against him.

The seven men showed no hesitation in facing this challenge from their once comrade-in-arms because the cost of failure was not just their lives but also the future of the world and all pirates. There was no room for negotiation, and they had to go all out. Furthermore, they had to finish the battle quickly; otherwise, if reinforcements arrived, they would be doomed. They did not follow any tactics and went straight into the BOSS battle; the pirates were responsible for dealing with the guards.

However, they never expected the Pirate King to be so resilient. The defense of that armor made it difficult for them. The seven men had to take turns to rest and continue the fight, hoping to wear down the Pirate King slowly. The righteous pirates saw this situation and decided to sacrifice their lives to support the seven men and defend the entrance of the hall. Finally, after a night-long struggle, the Pirate King finally breathed his last breath at dawn.

The Pirate King finally fell, but the cost was huge, which the seven never expected. The melee not only caused heavy casualties among the pirates, but many people also fled because they were afraid of being pursued. The organization faced disintegration. The seven knew they had to rebuild the system to restrain these demonized bandits, so they put in a lot of effort to reorganize and manage the organization, renaming it the Jaegers. From then on, the seven men slowly led the pirates back onto the right track. Unfortunately, everyone's admiration for the Pirate King never ceased. To break the demon's control, the seven men removed the golden armor and the Pirate King's body from the base and secretly buried it.</li>
  </BookDescription_XFKOP.rulePack.rulesStrings>

<!-- Phoenix -->
  <BookDescription_XFPhoenix.rulePack.rulesStrings>
        <li>desc->Since the Master discovered that XvA's appetite was related to her activity, he gave her many books and movies to keep her big appetite in check. XvA loved them very much, even though she could not understand them, she would spend a few hours reading them each time, and the Master would also use this opportunity to relax. One day, XvA came to the Master with a book about the history of XEO.

"Teacher, can you show me Four-Leafed Clover? I can't find it even on Google," XvA said.

"That stuff doesn't exist in the world, it's all made up," the Master answered casually. However, when he saw XvA look skeptical, he was afraid that she would go looking for answers and end up causing trouble.

The Master suddenly became serious: "Four-Leafed Clover is actually a drug called Luciferium. Once someone takes it, they become addicted and can never be saved. You must not touch that stuff."

"Ah, so the original creators used it to poison their targets. Impressive!" XvA looked very excited. The Master told her unkindly, "Well...let me put it this way, assassins in the past had the habit of taking this drug, but now the organization fears affecting its reputation, so they made up these stories."

"Our organization once caused great chaos due to the sale and use of this drug, which led to severe control by the Elder Council on Luciferium. XEO was printed on the packaging as a warning label for assassins to stay away from the temptation of the devil. X means prohibition, E is for Eat, and O is for Output, reminding assassins to avoid the lure of evil. Later, because it was deeply rooted in people's hearts, it became the Guild's nickname," the Master explained.

"Scary! Drug trafficking gangs? Drug-taking assassins? Aren't we a just organization?" XvA was disappointed. The Master continued, "You have to understand that people who write history are influenced by their environment and position, and they describe the same thing differently. Just like our founder, the Phoenix, there is another legend in the eyes of Star Explorers. When you read books, you must consider these factors."

"What legend? Can you tell me about it?" XvA leaned forward. Seeing this curious and cute girl, the Master was willing to spend some time training her thinking, and began to tell her a story.

The exploration team was being chased by Scythers when they stumbled into an ancient ruin in a panic. Inside, they found a cryopod with a white-haired girl wearing a red cloak sound asleep. As the Scythers closed in, the team opened the cryopod hoping to use the girl as a distraction, but to their surprise, she didn't run away. Instead, she violently ripped apart the Scythers with her bare hands in a gruesome display of violence, leaving the team terrified. After the Scythers were all destroyed, the team approached the girl curiously and asked about her background, but she seemed confused and couldn't even remember her own name. She only accompanied them as they searched the ruins where they found large amounts of Luciferium and resources, which made everyone excited. In gratitude to the girl, the team decided to bring her back to their base.

After returning to the base, people's understanding of the girl remained limited. She only expressed a need for more Luciferium, so they decided to keep the batch to not only protect her, but also others from her potential berserk behavior. The girl had a special feature - when she took off her helmet, people noticed a beautiful gem embedded on her forehead, which became a hot topic at the base. Many believed that it was a cognitive implant, and that the girl may have suffered severe brain damage, hence her confused state. In the following months, the girl single-handedly took on and defeated the attacking Mechanoids. Each time, she returned from the fiery scene like a phoenix, earning her nickname. Her exceptional abilities drew admiration and some started to learn from her how to use equipment and weapons to fight against the Mechanoids.

Thus, the Phoenix became more than just one person, but a force that protected the area beyond the base. Before fighting Mechanoids, they would use a special gunshot as a warning signal to alert civilians to flee. Their battle tactics involved surrounding and destroying the Mechanoids with a large number of close combat units. In a matter of months, all Mechanoid attacks in the nearby areas were stopped by them. The Phoenix's actions were seen as a retaliation against the Mechanoids, and people began to join the base in response to their call. The influx of people from different regions and backgrounds led to the emergence of new ideas among the masses. They propagated equality and shifted their target from the Mechanoids to those in power, turning the once peaceful base into an aggressive force.

This rapid expansion caught the attention of some scholars who felt that something was not right. The Phoenix did not accept any rewards after helping the towns, but instead recruited more people and collected machine debris as battle supplies. Her followers treated her like family, and their connection was abnormally tight. These people also imitated her by taking red diamond-shaped pills - Luciferium, which made them seem insane. The organization's fanaticism had exceeded normal levels and left the scholars feeling uneasy.

The scholars began their discussion, and for a while everyone was stuck on political arguments. Finally, a slightly crazy scientist interrupted the conversation with his bold theory that the ruins where they found the Phoenix resembled a spaceship structure, containing a large amount of resources and only one cryopod, which seemed very unreasonable. He speculated that it was an ecological transformation ship, and the Phoenix was the spaceship's artificial intelligence, possibly using the planet's intelligent life to create a suitable living environment for its master. Everyone laughed at his theory, but the scientist ignored their ridicule and continued to articulate his ideas. When he mentioned the gem on the Phoenix's forehead and the change in her followers, everyone started to feel afraid.

The scientist's speculation was not unfounded. The Phoenix not only knew the Mechanoids' attack patterns but could also accurately predict their arrival every time. This ability was inexplicable, and maybe the scientist was right - The exploration team had opened Pandora's Box, and the Phoenix was using humans to eliminate threats to the area and spread the Creator's return. Anything was possible, especially given the current level of fanaticism among the masses and the aggressiveness of their base. After this discussion, the scholars reached a consensus and decided to conduct further research into the ruins in the form of scientific research. As the project was related to the Phoenix, it quickly received funding from the ruling party.

Soon a team of explorers was organized, led by a guide who took them to the ruins. The scholars carefully examined each part of the ruins, finally coming up with a surprising result - the ruins were indeed part of a spacecraft wreckage that had been here for hundreds of thousands of years. Further evidence alerted the scholars, and they began discussing ways to deal with the Phoenix's organization, realizing that it had become a thorny problem. Without external intervention, they would not be able to stop her.

The team simulated various plans and finally chose a method that could kill two birds with one stone and minimize casualties. Over the next few days, they repaired the spacecraft's equipment while collecting data for analysis in hopes of finding a connection between the spacecraft wreckage and the Mechanoids. In the end, their efforts paid off as they found a way to connect the two and made a remote control device. On the day of the plan's execution, the scholars used the device to send a distress signal from the spacecraft wreckage, attracting the Phoenix and her followers. When the Phoenix entered the spacecraft, they summoned several groups of Mechanoids, turning the spacecraft wreckage into a battlefield.

In the end, not only did the spacecraft crash and burn, but the entire army of the Phoenix was destroyed in the battle. This massive battlefield also attracted the attention of other bandits who waited for an opportunity to scavenge the remaining Mechanoids and clean up the area. When everything returned to calm, the scholars who had been secretly observing approached to search for the Phoenix's body, hoping to find evidence to support their argument. The battlefield was littered with piles of dismembered limbs, and it took the team a long time to find her broken body. At first glance, the body seemed like ordinary flesh and blood, with organs no different from those of a normal person. However, upon careful examination, the scholars discovered that the nano-machines in the body were several times over the normal limit. Even a person who had been consuming Luciferium for a long time could not have reached this concentration. Such a large amount of nano-machines required a high-speed computing device to ensure their synergy. The scholars speculated that the gem on the Phoenix's head was that device, or even her consciousness itself. Unfortunately, the gem was no longer on her battered skull, and they searched everywhere but to no avail. It was impossible to know whether the gem was destroyed by the Mechanoids or taken by the bandits.

Without critical evidence, the team had no choice but to bring the Phoenix's body back to their base, hoping to persuade the masses to accept their viewpoint. However, they were wrong. The fanatical people who believed in the Creator did not accept the scholars' explanation. When they saw the gruesome body of the Phoenix, they burst into tears and cursed them: "Your future generations will all be assassinated." 

As the situation escalated, the crowd became more hostile towards the research team and demanded that they leave the base. Some even threatened to kill them. The researchers were terrified by their fanaticism and had never expected the situation to turn out this way. It seemed that ignorance had deeply ingrained itself in the people's beliefs, rendering reason useless. Realizing that it was hopeless to try and convince the masses, the researchers decided to disengage from the matter and left the area together.

"What did you learn from this story?" The master asked. "Did those scholars not know about the terrible relative generator?" XvA replied straightforwardly. "Relative generator!?" The master took a moment to understand what XvA was referring to and then said, "You're partly correct. The scholars were too fixated on the Phoenix and neglected the followers. As a result, they not only killed her but also the loved ones of the crowd, fueling their hatred and leading to irreparable damage. But do you know why it happened?" XvA thought for a long time but couldn't answer. The master continued, "It's because their thinking was constrained by their preconceived knowledge, causing them to have a one-sided perspective and overlook the viewpoints of others." "Just like the four-leaf clover in the book, which is actually Luciferium, the "Knell of Death" may have been a warning for people to evacuate, and the black apple might be the gem on the Phoenix's head. Each thing has its own interpretation from different angles, and you need to observe carefully and combine your own conclusions. Do you understand?" The master added. "Yes, teacher, I understand." XvA suddenly stared at the master, causing him to feel uneasy. Indeed, over the next few days, the master became XvA's subject of observation, so much so that he couldn't even look at his private collection(Porn). Eventually, the master could no longer tolerate it and gave XvA a stern lesson.</li>
  </BookDescription_XFPhoenix.rulePack.rulesStrings>

<!-- Tale of White -->
  <BookDescription_XFTOW.rulePack.rulesStrings>
        <li>desc->He was clad in white armor as he navigated through the key battle between the Diamond Bone and the Resistance Army. His extraordinary movements and marksmanship put immense pressure on the Diamond Bone army. Whenever the Resistance Army gained an advantage on the battlefield, he would suddenly disappear without a trace.

After the war ended, the white warrior never appeared again. Despite their curiosity, people couldn't find out who the owner of the armor was. No amount of praise or incentive could make him reappear. He remained a mystery throughout, and was known as nothing more than a myth - "Don't be obsessed with him, he's just a legend."

He was such a mysterious and unconstrained figure. To commemorate this warrior, the Resistance Army named him "Free Will" after gaining independence.</li>
  </BookDescription_XFTOW.rulePack.rulesStrings>

<!-- Snake and Apple -->
  <BookDescription_XFSAA.rulePack.rulesStrings>
        <li>desc->After being exiled by the Star Explorer, Vic's amnesia became very severe. He not only often fell into a coma, but also had comas that lasted for several days. Whenever he woke up, his backpack would have more things in it. Vic knew what had happened. When he was still an executive officer, his psychiatrist warned him that if he didn't take his medication, he would become a "moe moe da" (crazy). However, he ignored the warning because if people found out he was crazy in this profit-driven city of the Star Explorer, family members of the criminals he had killed could sue him and ruin his reputation, job, and life. He might even end up going back to his teenage years of scavenging and robbing - just like now.

Vic's hidden personality was extremely bloodthirsty. Every time he regained control of his body, he would see broken and fragmented corpses. Although Vic had seen similar scenes before, the frequency of these occurrences made him uneasy. Vic didn't understand why the other personality wanted him to see those images. It might be intimidation or an attempt to assimilate him. However, no matter what the reason was, Vic didn't care. He was a kind person but not a coward. Even though he had a mental illness, it did not affect him much. The mere gruesome scenes had no effect on him.

During this period, Vic tried to adapt to the situation of his body and took advantage of his limited freedom to investigate the clues of the manipulator. Vic tried to attack the people who were chasing him, but they were just bounty hunters who were after the reward on his wanted poster. Vic's wanted poster was issued by the Star Explorer special police force, and as a former executive officer, he understood how it worked. When a target needed to be wanted or eliminated, this kind of bounty would be issued. He didn't know whether it was the intention of the special police or the command of the council, but he knew one thing for sure: someone still wanted to kill him even after he was exiled. Unless the other party died or gave up, this matter would never end.

Vic had thought about going back to the Star Explorer to find out what happened, but unfortunately he had lost everything he had before. His friends had cut off ties with him because of his exile. Even if he sneaked back into the Star Explorer again, without his connections and power, he would only be trapped and unable to move forward. Therefore, he dismissed this idea and pinned his hopes on the Red Scorpion, the female assassin from XEO who had originally tried to kill him but then let him go.

The reason why Vic had confidence in the information provided by the assassin was due to his understanding of XEO. The team he used to belong to was responsible for investigating assassination activities, so he knew the dark secrets of XEO like the back of his hand. This organization advocated the doctrine of the Creator only to stabilize members' thoughts and maintain others' impression of them. In reality, they would accept money to kill people. Due to their willingness to use any means necessary and their religious beliefs, their mission success rate was much higher than other mercenary organizations. However, it was not easy to contact them. The fees charged for their services and additional conditions were also high. When dealing with them, clients must provide enough information as a means of mutual threat. And that information was exactly what Vic hoped to obtain.

Fortunately, another personality had a similar idea in searching for the female assassin and was even more enthusiastic than Vic. Although they couldn't communicate directly, they could exchange information through documents and notes left behind. Vic usually left the information he found to this personality so that he could decide on the direction of their actions. Vic also gradually adapted to the situation of his body through this collaborative relationship. Of course, he had tried to understand this personality, but it didn't want to be questioned further. Vic was afraid of causing trouble and did not pursue it any further. He only knew that the personality's name was Zeo. The last thing Vic left for Zeo was the location where Red Scorpion was imprisoned before being executed by the Council of Elders. After that, he fell into a coma.

During his coma, Vic had a terrible dream. He found himself in a pitch-black environment with a fat man carrying a flamethrower standing with his back to him. In the background, there were two roasted chickens strung together, and surrounding the fat man were countless pieces of fried chicken forming a creepy pattern. Suddenly, the fat man turned around and shoved a piece of fried chicken into Vic's mouth. This scared him so much that he woke up. When he opened his eyes, he saw that he was kneeling on top of a woman lying down. She was struggling and screaming, which frightened Vic even more. Looking around to assess the situation, Vic realized that he was in a deserted countryside area with only a small stream nearby. After confirming that there was no danger, Vic calmed down and focused his attention back on the woman. This woman was not ordinary; she had a distinctive ponytail and hair as red as blood. It was the infamous Red Scorpion - XEO's most feared assassin. Zeo had successfully captured her...

Red Scorpion seemed to want to escape, so Vic held her down tightly, afraid that she might run away. As he held her down, Vic felt his hand slip and let go only to realize that the red on her head wasn't just her hair but blood... She was bleeding badly... If they didn't stop the bleeding soon, she would definitely die. But she struggled violently, making it impossible for Vic to take action. Vic shouted at her several times in hopes of calming her down, but it only made her more nervous, and the bleeding became even worse. Vic became anxious and had no choice but to use physical restraint - he hit her on the back of the head with the butt of his gun, knocking her unconscious in order to save her life.

Vic immediately opened her health status bar to check her injuries. The contents made him dumbfounded - severe malnutrition, broken hands, countless bruises, a mutilated face, and a terrible wound on her forehead with her skull exposed, revealing her brain. Despite all of this, she still had the strength to struggle, which greatly impressed Vic. Most people would have passed out from the pain. All of Red Scorpion's wounds told Vic that she had experienced terrible torture. At this moment, Vic suddenly felt a sinking feeling in his heart as he remembered those bloody scenes from before... He thought to himself, "Could it be Zeo who did this to Red Scorpion? If that's the case, it's going to be troublesome..."

Red Scorpion's condition was worsening, and she was having continuous spasms. Vic didn't think too much and quickly rummaged through his backpack, hoping to find some useful first aid supplies. Although it was his backpack, it was ironic that due to his dual personality, he was not sure what was inside. He had asked Zeo for a list, but the latter had ignored him, and because Zeo had a habit of collecting junk, the backpack was in a mess. It took Vic a long time to find a medical kit, but luckily, he had developed high medical skills from playing PUBG when he was young. Soon, Red Scorpion's wounds were well treated, but her condition still did not improve.

"If this woman dies, it will be very difficult to continue the investigation," Vic was in a state of anxiety. He emptied his backpack and searched for anything that could be of use. Then, a box of red diamond-shaped pills caught his attention - Luciferium. Zeo had somehow obtained this drug. Vic knew the powerful effects and dangers of this drug. It could significantly improve body functions and even heal wounds and old ailments, but once taken, one cannot stop taking it. If you stop, you die... It's like making a deal with the devil at the crossroads. However, in this situation, he had no other choice but to take the risk. After all, he only needed the information that Red Scorpion knew. Whether she lives or dies after that is her own business.

Vic broke through his psychological barrier and fed Red Scorpion the Luciferium. The drug lived up to its reputation, as her condition quickly stabilized. Vic then took her to a nearby cave to settle down. While Red Scorpion was unconscious, Vic took care of her and planned what to do next. He realized that he might be the one who injured her - in other words, his alter ego Zeo. This made it difficult for him to extract information from her, and worse yet, she might attack him if provoked. In any case, XEO's assassins were very dangerous. Although tying her up and interrogating her seemed like the simplest and safest solution, Vic quickly dismissed this idea. He was still shaken by the earlier injury inflicted on Red Scorpion, and he felt reluctant to torture her further. Additionally, Red Scorpion had spared his life earlier, which made him feel indebted to her. Therefore, Vic believed that approaching the situation from a different angle might lead to a solution.

After much consideration, Vic chose a more gentlemanly approach. To show goodwill, he gave Red Scorpion some supplies and returned the assassin equipment and weapons that he found in his backpack to her. Afterwards, Vic used his mining skills from childhood to dig multiple branching tunnels within the cave, creating a labyrinth. He then settled in a hidden spot not far from Red Scorpion, planning to observe her reactions and make his next move accordingly. If she attacked him, Vic would have the advantage in this maze-like cave. Even if she managed to escape, Vic still held the trump card of Luciferium, so his plan seemed foolproof.

With the help of the drug, Red Scorpion quickly recovered and regained consciousness. However, Vic had already disappeared from her view and was monitoring her movements from the shadows. He thought she might take the supplies and run away or search the cave, but her behavior was vastly different from what he anticipated. Instead of leaving the cave, she lingered in the same spot, causing Vic to feel uneasy. It was either a sign of brain damage or a plan forming in her mind...either way, it was bad news for Vic.

Red Scorpion's unexpected behavior forced Vic to rethink his plan. Considering that she might be pretending to be crazy in order to lure him out, he abandoned the idea of meeting her and decided to extend his observation to determine the situation. Over the next few days, Red Scorpion remained in the cave, enjoying the food that Vic had left for her and spending her free time meditating. Vic observed her and learned that there was nothing wrong with her mind, but her harmless behavior was vastly different from her cold-blooded legend, making her even more suspicious.

Vic calculated the time and realized that the symptoms of Luciferium addiction should have already appeared in her body. He didn't want to harm her, so he planned to give her a dose of the drug to let her know that her life was being threatened.

Vic placed a Luciferium in a corner of the cave and intentionally made some noise. In no time, the Red Scorpion ran over to investigate. She spotted a small red piece on the ground, picked it up, and quickly returned to her spot. However, her seemingly "simple" action surprised Vic because she didn't bring any weapons when she came out and didn't pay attention to her surroundings. He couldn't help but ask himself, "Is she really an assassin? She seems too careless." Vic followed her to see what she was up to. After returning to her spot, the Red Scorpion knelt by the campfire, played with the Luciferium for a while before tossing it into the flames. Vic felt uneasy and quickly retreated.

Red Scorpion's behavior left Vic puzzled. He knew that XEO had a tradition of not taking Luciferium, but in life or death situations, people wouldn't abide by their creed, right? Perhaps she intentionally destroyed the drug to break free from being controlled. Vic was aware that if she refused to take the medication, the situation would become more complicated. He only wanted information, and it made sense to exchange it with Luciferium. However, he couldn't figure out Red Scorpion's thoughts. XEO members often stick to their creed, and her strange behavior added more uncertainty, especially since he had previously pressed her down. In terms of combat, facing her head-on was disadvantageous for Vic as he knew how formidable she was after their last encounter. He understood that this matter needed to be resolved and could no longer be delayed because addiction to Luciferium's symptoms could surface at any time, making things even worse. Therefore, with mental preparation, Vic took half of the Luciferium and kept the other half as a backup in the cave. He then picked up his weapon and headed towards the scorpion.

Vic watched Red Scorpion from a distance, and she still didn't carry any weapons. Although it was like this, he didn't approach her, but shouted loudly, "Let's cut to the chase. I'll exchange information for Luciferium." Red Scorpion looked towards Vic's position with a look of surprise and waved her hand vigorously, saying, "Ah! The man in black!" Vic was taken aback and puzzled by her expression and actions, but it didn't seem like she was pretending. After a while, Vic regained his composure and realized that the situation was better than he had expected. He immediately adjusted his strategy and walked over to sit cross-legged by the campfire, bringing up the topic of her injuries. This conversation went smoother than Vic had anticipated. Without using any tricks, the female assassin voluntarily revealed how she had been imprisoned and escaped. From her words, Vic learned about Zeo's prowess. That guy had once infiltrated the Elder Association's prison alone and provided Red Scorpion with the opportunity to escape. Moreover, the injuries on Red Scorpion's body were not caused by Zeo. At this point, Vic suddenly remembered that Zeo hadn't appeared for a long time, as if he had disappeared. Although this felt good for Vic, he couldn't shake off the feeling that something was amiss with Zeo's absence.

Regarding the female assassin known as Red Scorpion, her name is XvA. Vic's impression of her mostly came from the reports of Star Explorer media, which portrayed her as a cold-blooded and cunning killer. However, now Vic knows he was deceived. This assassin is not only not cold-blooded but also excessively passionate, with no sense of caution, and gesticulates wildly while speaking. As an executor, Vic has faced many assassins who conveyed the impression of being like drug-addled professional killers - calculated, ruthless, and somewhat crazy. Therefore, it is unbelievable to him that this person could become an assassin. Nevertheless, Vic remains cautious and wanted to test if she was pretending to be foolish. "Why didn't you leave?" Vic implied in his words that he had been monitoring her, but XvA didn't catch on: "I wanted to find you, but I have a strange illness. I get hungry when I move too much, and I didn't know where you were. So, I prayed to the Creator to make you appear, and you did!" XvA seemed very excited. "... "Vic remained silent for a while. He realized that XvA wasn't pretending; she really was a bit foolish, and that's why her behavior was so strange. It was Vic himself who made things more complicated.

After understanding her thoughts, Vic no longer beat around the bush and directly asked, "I know you were executed for releasing me in violation of orders. Why did you do that?" XvA suddenly leaned closer to Vic and asked, "Have we met before?" Her action reminded Vic of their first meeting, which made him feel uncomfortable. "Big sis, I am very sure that our first encounter was during your assassination attempt," Vic replied. XvA recoiled and said, "Little bro, that day you gave me a sense of familiarity. I felt like you knew about my past." XvA used "Little bro" to address Vic after he called her "Big sis". Vic became awkward and said, "That term doesn't mean what you think it does...never mind. So, you spared me because you found me familiar? That's it?" Her reason left Vic puzzled. "Yes," XvA answered affirmatively. "Then who commissioned the assassination against me?" Vic pressed on. XvA propped up her chin and said, "Hmm...I don't know. I always use autopilot for mission tasks, without checking the content." Hearing this, Vic felt thunderstruck. In his impression, assassins all adhere to rules, even if they are absurd, like the Knell of Death rule. But now, this assassin in front of him...

"This was an assassination mission against a council member, right? Political assassinations should be S-class in your line of work. Did you really not read any of the content? Did you forget something?" Vic didn't quite believe that an assassin would behave this way, so he continued to question XvA, hoping to get some useful information. "I receive too many missions and lose patience with reading all of them. It's become a habit," XvA replied plainly. Vic still didn't give up and kept trying to coax her into revealing something useful, but he only received unhelpful answers. After a few back-and-forth exchanges, Vic finally gave up. He knew XvA wasn't lying. During those months, XvA had broken records by assassinating more people than anyone in decades, even Vic as an executor couldn't remember how many people she had killed. Initially, XvA could have been a good informant, but now, she couldn't return to the organization. Her situation was equally dire as Vic's, so this lead was completely cut off. Vic stood up and was contemplating his next steps. He looked at the Luciferium in his hand, which was worthless except for selling it for a few bucks. He decided to give it all to this Miss as a way to repay her kindness."

"After you spared me that time, and I saved you this time, we're even now," said Vic as he tossed the whole box of Luciferium to her, cautioning her, "Remember to take it on time. I still have more in my camp, I'll go get it for you." Vic turned around and left.

"Little brother, I escaped from the laboratory, and I want to find my past. Can you help me?" XvA rushed forward and grabbed Vic's clothes. Vic hesitated for a moment, but he knew he was being hunted down, and getting involved with her would not be beneficial for either of them. "I'm sorry, I have my own business to handle," Vic declined vaguely. "Take me with you, don't you have any troubles? Maybe I can help!" XvA pleaded. "That's a personal grudge, you don't have to worry about it," Vic replied resolutely, but seeing XvA's pitiful expression made him soften a bit. He thought giving her a direction could be an easy task, so he opened her skill panel and saw that all her skills were at level zero except for combat, which was maxed out. This value made Vic silent for a while. He turned to look at XvA's long ears and sharp teeth...this creature was produced in a genetic factory for wealthy people to play with and consume, there was no real past to speak of.

"Miss, I advise you not to be stubborn. In your situation, your past may have just been a pile of nutrient solution..." Vic spoke harshly, hoping that she would face reality. However, XvA didn't listen and replied, "That's not true. My master said that even someone who pops out of a rock here will have relatives."

Hearing this, Vic fell into deep thought. A wave of sadness washed over him as he remembered his lost parents and the painful experiences of his childhood struggle for survival. XvA's situation resonated with him, and he thought to himself, "This miss became like this because she spared me. If I leave her alone, she definitely won't survive." XvA's innocent reason touched Vic, and he decided to let her stay while he went back to camp to gather supplies before leaving. XvA was overjoyed when she heard this and quickly turned around to pack her backpack.

Vic returned to his campsite and pulled out the hidden Luciferium. He knew that traveling with someone addicted to Luciferium would not be an easy task and he needed a plan. Fortunately, during his time living in a Star Explorer city, he had saved a large amount of silver, so money was not an issue. After making all necessary preparations, Vic returned to XvA's campsite. However, as he approached, he heard some sizzling sounds. Curious, he looked over and saw XvA barbecuing a box of Luciferium in the fire. Vic was scared and rushed over to scatter the fire, but unfortunately, several usable pieces of Luciferium were already burnt. "What are you doing?" Vic was angry. XvA's tone became stern: "Little brother, drugs harm people and have lifelong consequences. Good children should not use drugs. Besides, this is Luciferium. Using it will kill you!" It was only then that Vic remembered XvA burning medicine before. She must not have known that she had already taken it. Vic controlled his anger and understood that communication with these clone people required patience and insight due to their limited contact with the external world, which affected their thinking. Vic softened his tone and became gentle, "You were badly injured at that time, and I fed you these drugs so that you could survive." XvA was shocked and at first couldn't accept what she was hearing. "What? This...this..." Vic interrupted her, "Never mind that now. Anyway, you cannot stop taking medicine from now on." He then put a pill into XvA's mouth. XvA knew she was in trouble; she looked at the remaining burnt Luciferium pieces and let out a cry of despair like a deflated ball. To encourage her, Vic took out another box of Luciferium from his backpack and said, "Don't worry, you still have some time."

Vic sat down and asked XvA to tell him in detail about her escape from the laboratory. XvA began her performance, and Vic had never seen anyone speak with so many gestures before. "When I opened my eyes, everything was red. I was in a glass room, and assassins and some people in white armor were fighting outside. My leader..." "Leader?" Vic interrupted XvA's words. "I had a Fan club over there, and the leader of the association rescued me. Unfortunately, she is meeting with Creator now." XvA seemed sad and stunned until Vic called her back to reality.

"The leader broke open the door of the room, carried me on her back, and I saw her bleeding. After a short distance, she put me down and gave me her blade. I followed the leader's instructions and kept running. The place was already chaotic, with shouts everywhere. The leader told me not to care about anything and just keep going. Finally, we ran out of the laboratory. As soon as we got out, we were attacked by some green soldiers, but thankfully I knew how to deflect bullets, and we escaped from there."

"What is bullet deflection? How do you do it?" Vic had seen XvA deflecting bullets before but never understood how she did it. "Don't you know? All assassins can deflect bullets. I didn't even know what it was at first. It was my master who later taught me. Little brother, I'll show you how to do it if I have the chance." Vic was speechless at XvA's response, amazed at her ability to believe such absurd reasons.

According to XvA's description, Vic recalled an attack on the Diamond Bone laboratory, which was the beginning of the Diamond Bone War. As he had previously conducted investigations on the matter, he had a strong impression of it. Once they had a target, Vic quickly devised a route and began their journey. After several encounters on their journey, Vic discovered that XvA was really good at deflecting bullets. Her accuracy didn't seem like a skill she practiced, which aroused Vic's curiosity. "Miss, with you flashing around like that, my eyes hurt. Will I be killed if you get too close?" asked Vic in confusion. XvA confidently replied, "Don't worry little bro, my shooting may not be accurate, but my blade is precise." Although filled with doubts, Vic did not dare to risk his life.

Since Vic brought XvA along, the bounty hunters were no longer a threat. However, what worried him was XvA. She gave Vic the feeling of being a trained killing tool, lacking self-judgment standards and only seeing targets and non-targets in her eyes. In order to prevent XvA from engaging in meaningless killings, Vic would let the hunters go if they were willing to give up. He hoped that XvA could learn some basic moral concepts from him and adapt to human group life as soon as possible because Vic had no intention of always bringing her along. Before going back to investigate leads related to the manipulator in the Star Explorer faction, a group he belonged to, Vic planned to settle XvA first.

The journey did not go as smoothly as Vic had hoped. The biggest obstacle they faced on the way was not the attackers, but food - XvA's appetite was as frighteningly abnormal as she had claimed, and they had eaten through half of their provisions halfway through their journey. They were forced to stop at a makeshift market nearby, located on the main transportation route of Diamond Bone. The market was of a certain size, and many merchants came here to sell goods and supplies left over from the Diamond Bone War. Vic wanted to try his luck and see if he could find Luciferium besides food. He knew that these war-torn merchants were not the most trustworthy people, as their appearances were too distinct in the eyes of those people. To avoid trouble, they disguised themselves by putting on cloaks and only entered the market after nightfall.

These merchants did not disappoint Vic - they had large numbers of illicit items, including drugs, clothing stolen off dead bodies, heavy firepower weapons, and even prisoners of war. Vic didn't want to get involved in any complications and planned to leave quickly after making purchases. XvA obediently followed behind him without saying a word. Suddenly, Vic saw a shuttle approaching in the distance, and in an instant, the crowd became chaotic. Shortly afterward, everyone began dispersing in different directions. Vic carefully hid himself among the crowd and saw a person in a red robe with two guards slowly walking towards them. The person in the middle had a sour face, and the two guards wore heavy power armor and melee weapons that Vic had never seen before. It was clear that they were not easy to provoke.

The crowd continued to disperse left and right, with people around discussing in a fuss. Vic had a feeling that something was not right and was about to leave when he realized that XvA was missing. He anxiously looked around and soon spotted XvA standing in front of three individuals, looking dazed and not following the dispersing crowd. Vic's heart almost jumped out of his mouth upon seeing this. XvA sensed danger and had already taken off her cloak and drawn her blade. As expected, at the command of the Men in Red, two guards rushed towards XvA, causing a sudden outburst of clashing swords and blades in the marketplace. However, instead of dispersing, the crowd began to gather and recognized XvA as the "Red Scorpion." Some even started gambling, and even the peanut and soda vendor appeared to profit from the situation. The noisy surroundings made Vic very anxious, and he did not know what to do. Finally, XvA's cry woke him up, but luckily she only suffered a minor injury. Vic immediately analyzed the situation and realized that the two guards' attack was not fierce and they probably didn't know much about XvA's fighting style. Meanwhile, the Men in Red was busy surveying the crowd and didn't pay attention to their fight.

The Men in Red, who lacked protection, were a prime target for Vic. He planned to take them down first to free XvA, and even if he failed, the ensuing chaos would provide an opportunity for them to escape. Slowly moving towards the front of the crowd with his guns at the ready beneath his cloak, Vic waited until the Men in Red's gaze shifted away before unleashing a volley of shots. However, all he heard was a dull thud as their shields appeared, powered not just by belts but also infused with psychic energy that rendered them impervious to his attacks. At that moment, Vic thought his attack would scare the crowd, but boy was he wrong! Having lived in the city for too long, he forgot that these people were no ordinary folk - they were scavengers who rummaged through battlefields or smugglers who took risks for a living. Their guts might have been bigger than his head! Instead of fear, they cheered and pushed him forward with such force that he nearly fell. Seeing Vic's sorry state, the Men in Red merely sneered at him, treating him with disdain like a feeble weakling. The guards paid him no attention and continued their siege on XvA, whose fighting style they had grown accustomed to. As their attacks became more aggressive under their pincer-like assault, XvA's breathing and rhythm became erratic, and she barely managed to evade or block their attacks. The situation looked dire, and Vic knew he needed to create an opening for XvA to catch her breath. He fired at one of the guards, hitting him several times, but despite this, his armor was too thick, and he was only momentarily stunned. Irritated by the sneak attack, the guard called Vic a worthless fool and made a throat-slitting gesture towards XvA. 

Vic was helpless as he watched XvA being surrounded and attacked, with no means of intervening. A feeling of powerlessness overwhelmed him as the sounds around him made him dizzy and his heart raced uncontrollably. It was a familiar sensation, one of watching loved ones leave without being able to do anything about it. Suddenly his mind went blank, and all sound stopped. Everything became silent. 'Friend, you can't handle this. Let me take over.' Vic recognized the voice - it was the 'friend' from the archaeological team he knew when he was younger. 'Zeo!?' Vic instinctively blurted out the name.

Vic silently agreed in his heart, and his consciousness seemed to have retreated behind a glass curtain. He saw his hands raising the gun and aimed at the crowd. Then there was a frenzy of shooting. The guy selling peanuts was the first to get shot in the head, and peanut and brain splattered into the air. The crowd panicked and scattered, some running away while some picked up weapons. The chaos made the guards stop their attack on XvA, giving her a chance to catch her breath. She seized the opportunity, accompanied by singing, and swung her high freguency blade to cut off one person's legs. Another person immediately regained his senses and noticed the situation. At this moment, Zeo fired several shots at the guard's head, then ran towards him without looking back. XvA thought he was going to run away, so she followed closely. After a few seconds, a series of explosions came from behind them. The traders had already taken out the triple rocket launcher and the ruins maker to greet them. The Men in Red instantly lost his previous imposing manner, becoming no different from the people around him who were trying to escape. Without hesitation, Zeo sent two bullets into his head. He would never again have the chance to use his psychic abilities.

The crowd had dispersed, and the angry mob started to fire at XvA and Zeo. XvA sliced through all the bullets that came her way, giving Zeo a chance to run towards a defensive position. After taking out the machine gunner, they both jumped into the small space of the defense position and huddled together. XvA was trembling with fear, while Zeo kicked her out to use her as a shield and picked up the machine gun on the cover to shoot back at the enemy. In the midst of the firefight, Zeo even took the time to finish off the guard with a broken leg. Zeo was in a killing frenzy, and Vic, who was still conscious, watched in horror as he realized how terrifying his "friend" could be. Now there were only two targets left for the merchants: Zeo and XvA. They were like sitting ducks in the eyes of the merchants, with bullets raining down on them. XvA could handle the situation, but she appeared anxious. Vic knew that even if she was extremely skilled, her weapon would not be able to sustain the constant attacks from the merchants. Moreover, there was a higher likelihood that the merchants possessed other explosives, and reinforcements could arrive at any moment. Vic kept telling Zeo to retreat, but he seemed to ignore him and continued to shoot everything in sight. Vic decided to stop him and tried to focus his consciousness on his hand, which worked after a while, allowing him to regain control of his body. Vic led XvA to retreat while fighting, and eventually, they rode on a muffalo from the merchant convoy to escape the market. However, the merchants didn't give up and mounted their animals to pursue them. In the darkness, Vic drove the muffalo to gallop wildly until it was exhausted, and they were forced to stop. At this point, there were no more pursuers behind them, but they didn't know where they had ended up.

This planet has many uncharted areas, and it is extremely dangerous to stray from the main roads without prior location. This is also why merchants give up pursuit. Vic knew the danger and followed the muffalo's tracks in hopes of finding the main road. However, having lived in cities all his life, he was not skilled at wilderness tracking. The weak night light made it easy for him to lose his way, and subsequent heavy rainfall washed away all traces. There were no forests in this wilderness, and they began to suffer from hypothermia due to being soaked by rain. Vic stopped and checked the muffalo's pack, which was almost empty as traders would take everything useful to sell. Only camping equipment and a crude map remained, but it was enough to comfort Vic. He set up a tent and started a fire, while XvA had already fallen asleep, exhausted. However, Vic couldn't sleep and kept watch over the fire to prevent it from being extinguished by pooling water. Since learning that Zeo was his childhood "friend," Vic's thoughts have been racing. He recalled the black stone he dug up in the city ruins and his confused memories. He believed there must be some connection between them, and Zeo must know something that he doesn't. The answer may have been with him all along.

What happened at the market made Vic realize that he could communicate directly with Zeo. He tried again, but no matter what he thought or said out loud, he received no response. Finally, he yelled out in frustration. "You are really annoying." Suddenly, Zeo's voice entered Vic's ear, but it was through Vic's own mouth and the tone was noticeably different. Vic knew he was talking to himself. "Do you know what I'm thinking? How am I supposed to communicate with you?" As childhood friends, Vic felt comfortable asking directly about their communication method. "I won't know what you're thinking. Our memories and thoughts are separate, so you have to say it out loud," Zeo replied. After hearing this, Vic was even more certain that he could get some information from Zeo. "Why haven't you been taking control of the body? I thought you were dead." On the market, Zeo needed Vic's permission to take over control of the body. This was something Vic was well aware of, and he asked just to see Zeo's reaction. The previous conversation had proven that Zeo could communicate with him freely, but Zeo had remained silent, obviously not wanting to be discovered. "You don't need to play these games anymore. I have the consciousness now to talk to you on my own," Zeo saw through Vic's tactics. "We are sharing senses now, as you know, and the domination of the body is no longer in my hands." "So you're saying I've evolved from a split personality to schizophrenia!? That's just amazing," Vic said self-deprecatingly, finding it hard to accept.

"If you don't want to beat around the bush, I won't either. There is a gap between my memories of my parents and the reality, and the missing memories should be with you. I want to know what happened," Vic asked directly. "They're dead, that's it," Zeo's answer obviously did not satisfy Vic: "Friend, don't play games with me. That's not what I want to hear. And what about the black stone? You know why we came to this wilderness from the warm bed." "Well, that's easy. Who would have thought that you knew the archaeological team was wiped out because of that stone? We were originally survivors, but you meddled and exposed us," Zeo got emotional as he spoke. He continued, "Do you remember the fight at the orphanage? Since then, I knew you were no good. Your sense of justice would eventually kill us." Zeo was right. Vic also knew that the trouble was his own doing. "Do you want me to just live in confusion? I can't do that. To be frank, it's because of my search for my parents that I found the motivation to survive." Because of his childhood experiences, Vic had become suspicious, and he felt an alienation from others. Even though he made many friends in the Star Explorer, loneliness always seemed to follow him. Zeo fell silent for a moment before speaking calmly again, "It's come to this, so be it. But I still don't trust you. Kindness has affected your judgment, and now that you are leading the body, the situation is even worse." Zeo finally cooperated, and Vic took a step back, saying, "I'm listening."

"The attacker can trace your whereabouts because of the bounty hunters you let go and the number of people you killed at the market earlier, remember? Those merchants now hold a grudge against you and will gladly reveal your location if they're alive. That's why I had to eliminate them all," said Zeo confidently. He added, "I showed you the bodies of those hunters to get you accustomed to this kind of situation. Trust me, the only way to survive is to make people fear you." Upon hearing this, Vic felt disgusted. As he had anticipated, Zeo's reasoning made sense, but it would only isolate him from others. "Do you want me to become like you? Absolutely not possible. Your bloodthirsty personality makes it difficult for you to live in a community. That's why you always let me to take over the body when we lived in Star Explorer. You know that too well. Some things are just too extreme, and do we not have enough enemies already?" Vic rebutted Zeo's argument. However, after the battle in the market, he also realized his weakness. Kindness limited his thinking, and he dared not even think of certain actions. "I have my limits in these matters. Worst case scenario, I'll let you take over my body." "Sounds good to me. I'm eager to see that," Zeo accepted Vic's compromise. Vic then continued, "So, we have a consensus now? Tell me everything you know."

Zeo remained silent for a while, and Vic couldn't wait any longer: "You don't have a choice now. I have the dominant power over our body. You can't let me be clueless, not sharing information will only make us fail together." "Friend, don't worry. I'm trying to figure out how to tell you," Zeo began slowly. "First of all, you were only exiled with the help of someone." "What?" Vic was shocked by Zeo's words. "Of course, it's just a speculation. We were both in the limelight at that time, so it wasn't easy to investigate," Zeo said. It turned out that Zeo's words were only speculation, and Vic didn't agree: "This doesn't make sense. I was just fired, but then I was accused and exiled. Isn't that making things worse?" Zeo said, "The manipulator's goal is to kill us. Is a pig in a pigsty easier to slaughter than a wild boar in the wilderness?" After listening to Zeo, Vic understood a bit more, and Zeo continued speaking: "My intuition tells me that someone has interfered in this matter, which is why our lawsuit is hitting a wall everywhere. That person wants to increase your guilt and make you escape from the manipulator's control. Look at you now, aren't you running around in the wilderness with a wanted poster hanging on your head?" After hearing Zeo's explanation, Vic understood why he made such a speculation. "Another thing is related to the information about the XEO given to you by your special police friend. I learned about it when I was looking for that idiotic girl. S-level missions like political assassinations would not be recorded by the elders. Only the elders, the commissioned assassin, and the client know the content. Anyway, your friend is also well-connected. Did he say how he got the information?"

At that time, Vic's friend only mentioned that they obtained the information at risk, without going into detail about the process, and the intelligence documents were also incomplete. After Zeo spoke up, Vic also became suspicious. Zeo added, "Do you see? If you appeal with that document, the worst charge would be dereliction of duty. The manipulator wants to keep us in the Star Explorer until the heat dies down, and then get rid of us. You know better than anyone the trouble with the special police." Vic knew that the special police force was very corrupt, with incidents of rape, bribery, drug trafficking, and more. In the eyes of the public, they were always ridiculed as privileged police. However, the people around Vic identified themselves as regular police, so he never expected it to be this way. "Either way, you can't go back now. Star Explorer is like a giant arena, with spies fighting and politicians playing power games. Someone like you, who has lost their status, won't be able to survive there. Promise me this first, and then I'll continue talking," Zeo advised seriously. He could tell that Vic was considering going back into danger after losing the lead, but if Zeo's speculation was correct, going back would be a dead-end for him.

"I'll promise you that," Vic agreed with Zeo. "Good. As for that Black Stone, it has been kept hidden in the Star Explorer's database since the archaeological team was attacked. It was stolen during the recent transfer, which was the transport ship accident that the military believes was done by the Diamond Bone people." Vic interrupted Zeo's words: "Aren't these all top secrets? Where did you get your information?" "From the database administrator," Zeo's reply almost made Vic curse. He finally realized that this guy was the one who had blown up the incident. "I like being direct. The image of his wife and children begging for mercy is still in my mind." Zeo's words were full of pride, making Vic unable to control his anger: "No wonder I got assassinated! And you have the nerve to say that I'm meddling!?" "Calm down. You started it first. I have no reason not to participate, and besides, you have already alerted them. They will find us sooner or later. I'm just speeding things up, and my methods are more effective than yours." Zeo's defense left Vic speechless. Zeo was right. Without taking risks like him, it was impossible to obtain this information.

Zeo continued, "After that comes the matter of trafficking children. Diamond Bone buys orphans and street children from Star Explorer for their experiments to save money. Star Explorer is happy to get rid of these societal burdens. One of the orphanages we stayed at was involved in this. You should know about it, right?" Vic had a deep understanding of this matter in his search for the little girl's whereabouts. He even publicly exposed the incident, but the manipulators used the commotion created by the Red Scorpion to cover it up. He told Zeo all the details. "This is interesting. Can you guess where the Black Stone was taken?" Zeo asked with a mysterious tone. "Do you mean that the people from our childhood orphanage were taken to the same laboratory as the Black Stone?" Vic guessed Zeo's meaning. "The information from the Star Explorer is indeed like that, quite a coincidence, right? Later, the council wanted to retrieve the Black Stone, but didn't want to provoke the Diamond Bone. So they used the XEO assassins as a decoy, and then they took advantage of the chaos to rob it, but they didn't expect the Jaeger to intervene suddenly," Zeo added, "Anyway, the Star Explorer's retrieval plan failed because the Black Stone is now inside the brain of that idiot." After hearing Zeo's words, Vic became alert because he had checked XvA's head wound and only saw smooth brain tissue without any black stone. If they shared senses, Zeo wouldn't have lied like this. Vic knew there must be a problem but didn't tell Zeo: "Do you know anything about this stone? Why do so many people want it?"

"Want it? No, except for Diamond Bone's crazy behavior, I don't think anyone would want it. The Star Explorer Council's purpose for recovering the black stone was to seal it away," Zeo said. Vic was a bit puzzled, and Zeo continued, "During my search for the mentally idiot, I asked about the stone at XEO. It's called the Black Apple there, and villagers believe that those who come into contact with it will be controlled by desire, leading to a tragic end. That's why all the legends surrounding it are bad things. I was curious and checked some wild histories for comparison. The truth is, every time the Black Apple appears, it causes a chain reaction, causing certain people or forces to disappear." Vic asked, "The Star Explorer had already obtained the black stone back then, and I remember XEO's assassins also came to the archaeological site. Since this is already known to everyone and no one wants to touch this stone, why did they want to silence the archaeological team? And why did they find us after so many years? It can't be just to hide information, right?" "Haha, because they're not afraid of the Black Stone, but of those who have come into contact with it," Zeo laughed. "They silenced people for such a small thing?" Vic was a bit skeptical, and Zeo said, "Those who have come into contact with the Black Stone in the database have a certain degree of mental infection. The Star Explorer even locked up those researchers and scientists. What more for a mere archaeological team?" Vic understood Zeo's words because he was also one of the victims.

Vic asked, "Have you investigated the unknown forces that attacked us back then?" "Twin Stars," said Zeo, "they were a special operations and espionage group, but that organization has long been disbanded. All their data was destroyed, including the databases." Zeo's information was similar to Vic's, but Vic had conducted more investigations into the matter. He shared his views with Zeo: "I suspect that this organization triggered the Diamond Bone War. They likely just went underground, and if we can find one of them, we may be able to find the manipulator." "Haha, don't tell me you think the manipulator is just one person?" Zeo laughed, thinking Vic's ideas were too naive. "Regardless, someone must be making decisions," Vic insisted. Zeo continued, "If you knew the strangeness of the Black Apple, you wouldn't think that way. The Diamond Bone incident was a warning." "Don't be superstitious. The manipulator already had an agent planted in the Diamond Bone incident, which made it easy to start the war," Vic countered. "Hey, it's not about how we see things, but how scared people see things. Maybe it's a group of people with panic disorder who want to kill us," Zeo chuckled, questioning Vic, "Didn't we just provoke the Empire?" "What? As far as I know, besides XvA, there should be no other survivors in that laboratory. How could anyone have known?" Vic was shocked. "That idiot didn't explain it clearly to you. There was an elder who knew about her brain having a black stone in it. When I saved her, there were only Templar Musha around and I had no chance to kill that elder. He must have passed on the information to the Empire. This makes me more certain that the manipulator is a group." "Based on what you're saying, we have no chance of winning..." Vic knew his limits. Faced with such a large organization, they could only run for their lives.

"This is very realistic, and it's also what I've been wanting to tell you. I'm not planning to confront them anymore. Friend, the most important thing is to stay alive," Zeo voiced his thoughts. Seeing Vic didn't respond, Zeo continued, "And that idiot, her luck ends here. Luciferium combined with Black Apple is fucking deadly. If you bring her with us, even we won't be able to protect ourselves." After a long silence from Vic, Zeo knew he was hesitant: "I've said everything I know. You decide what to do next. I can't help you in this wasteland. I'm going to sleep now." "Aren't we sharing senses? How can you sleep?" Vic was curious. "Our consciousness is separate. I can cut off my senses whenever I want," Zeo explained and then said, "Look at that horizon. It's already questionable if you can make it out of here alive. Sometimes you have to be ruthless. Compassion doesn't put food on the table." Zeo hinted for him to abandon XvA. "Wait, about our parents..." Vic saw that Zeo purposely avoided the topic, but Zeo interrupted him, "Friend, I've spared you the hardest part. Don't dig too deep or you might awaken something sinister. Remember, hunger is a terrifying thing. Good luck." After saying this, Zeo didn't respond no matter how much Vic called out to him.

After Zeo disappeared, Vic sat by the campfire and pondered his situation. Zeo wasn't so much a friend as he was a guardian to Vic. Although he was crazy, Zeo did things that Vic would never have dared to do himself. He was always there to guide and protect him, so there was no reason for Zeo to lie to him. However, Zeo was keeping something hidden, and if it weren't for the danger they faced at the market, Vic would have remained in the dark.

Vic had an intuition that Zeo had more to confess than just about his parents' affairs. It seemed too coincidental that Zeo now possessed the power, and there must be a reason behind it. Vic recalled talking to Zeo in a similar manner when they were part of the archaeological team. At that time, Vic thought he was communicating with Black Stone until Twin Star attacked and took it away. Zeo disappeared at the same time, and Vic's memory became confused. This sudden change left him feeling uneasy.

There appeared to be some connection between Zeo and Black Stone. Comparing the past events to the present, Vic realized that Black Stone might be related to their power. When Zeo lost his powers, he must have recognized this fact, which explained why he kept silent. That also explained why he didn't suggest anything when Xva was severely injured. The fight at the market was terrifying. Vic wiped his forehead, realizing that he almost trusted Zeo and gave up on Xva. If Zeo regained the power this time, the worst-case scenario for Vic would be sleeping forever.

Although this was purely Vic's speculation, he had to be cautious because he had actually experienced the power of Black Stone. When he was wandering around with the archaeological team, he couldn't make friends and felt lonely. Out of desperation, he made a wish to Black Stone, and ended up with a friend, but only existing in his mind... and it wasn't just him. Even his parents became nervous after obtaining Black Stone, and the whole archaeological team encountered disaster as a result. The process was just like Zeo's legend of the black apple, where Black Stone satisfied the desires of those who came into contact with it in an eerie way and brought misfortune.

What made Vic uneasy was that his misfortune might have started recently. Thinking about this, Vic regretted digging out the Black Stone from the ruins. He couldn't help but sink deeper into his thoughts. He slapped his cheeks with both hands to wake himself up and reminded himself that all of this was just superstition. The manipulator was actually the one causing his misfortune.

By now, the rain had stopped, and the dawn light appeared on the horizon. Vic walked into the tent and saw XvA sleeping soundly, mouth wide open and drooling. It seemed that the fight at the market exhausted her. Vic was half-believing and half-doubting about Black Stone's existence in XvA's head, so he checked the wound on her forehead while she slept. Thanks to Luciferium, the wound had healed well, and there was no scar visible. Vic had no way to confirm the existence of Black Stone, and he couldn't afford to risk losing control again, so he chose to believe.

Seeing XvA's dirty face and drool, Vic picked up a towel and wiped her face. He was surprised to find that she was not just beautiful, but also completely symmetrical in her bone structure, facial features, body, and even skin pattern. Although gene editing was already very mature in this era, there were still many variables in the growth process of organisms, so such precision symmetry could not be achieved in natural environments or culture tanks. This kind of symmetry could only be found in bionic robots. Curious, Vic pinched XvA softly, feeling that her skin was soft and 100% pure and natural without any additives.

"How was this symmetry achieved? Is it biological printing technology? Why would labs with this technology still buy orphans?" Vic couldn't help but ask himself. Suddenly, an idea flashed through his mind, and he remembered the ugly little girl at the orphanage. "If Black Stone ended up in the hands of a girl who is both ugly and weak... No, it can't be that coincidental..." Thinking about this, Vic became increasingly frightened and uneasy. This Black Stone returned to him in an unbelievable way more than ten years later, and he began to understand why those manipulators were afraid.

The eerie atmosphere surrounded Vic, and ever since Zeo told him about Black Stone, he couldn't stop thinking about it. Vic unconsciously shook his head and said, "I'll go crazy if I keep going like this!" He decided not to dwell on these questions anymore and instead focused on escaping from the wilderness.

In order to make the most of the daylight hours, Vic decided to set off. He patted XvA to wake her up, but she didn't respond at all. Vic had to take some cooking utensils and knock on her ear a few times. Unexpectedly, XvA screamed in fear, trembling uncontrollably. Her reaction was too exaggerated. "Miss, I just asked you to wake up. Are you okay? Why are you shaking so badly?" XvA's voice trembled as she replied, "I had a terrible dream. I saw my blade break and my body being shot into two parts, crawling on the ground..."

"Since seeing my Leader die, I have had this strange illness," XvA hugged her knees tightly, hoping to stop trembling. Vic had seen her like this before in the market. Could it be PTSD? Vic knelt down and patted her shoulder to comfort her. "It's all over now." Suddenly, XvA looked at Vic with a determined expression. "I...want to live." Vic felt that XvA was different from before, no longer the silly girl with a big sister vibe, but it only lasted for a while. "Ha, I'm shaking so hard I might pee myself..."

"Take a deep breath and relax. The more you resist, the more you will shake," Vic said to XvA. She followed Vic's words, and her trembling gradually eased. Vic stood up and held XvA's hand to help her up. Vic replied with a confident tone, "I don't want to die either. Let's see what we can do." Vic extinguished the campfire, packed up the tent, and in order to reduce food consumption, he asked XvA to sit on top of the muffalo. Then, he opened the crude map and led the muffalo on their wilderness survival journey.</li>
  </BookDescription_XFSAA.rulePack.rulesStrings>

</LanguageData>