<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>
  <!-- Parry -->
  <XF_CutBulletChance>Bullet Deflection Chance: {0}%</XF_CutBulletChance>
  <XF_ParryChance>Parry Chance: {0}%</XF_ParryChance>
  <XF_StunChance>Stun Chance: {0}%</XF_StunChance>
  <NoApparelOrWeapon_Parry>Requires wearing power armor and equipping a melee weapon.</NoApparelOrWeapon_Parry>
  <NoMeleeWeapon_Parry>Requires equipping a melee weapon.</NoMeleeWeapon_Parry>
  <noparrygear>Requires wearing power armor.</noparrygear>
  <NoApparelOrWeapon_CutBullet>Requires wearing power armor and equipping an XF High Frequency Weapon, XF Red Stone Weapon or Bladelink Weapon.</NoApparelOrWeapon_CutBullet>
  <NoSpecialWeapon_CutBullet>Requires equipping an XF High Frequency Weapon, XF Red Stone Weapon or Bladelink Weapon.</NoSpecialWeapon_CutBullet>
  <nocutbulletgear>Requires wearing power armor.</nocutbulletgear>
  <NoApparelOrWeapon_Stun>Requires wearing power armor and equipping a melee weapon.</NoApparelOrWeapon_Stun>
  <NoMeleeWeapon_Stun>Requires equipping a melee weapon.</NoMeleeWeapon_Stun>
  <nostungear>Requires wearing power armor.</nostungear>
  <StatsReport_FromGear>Gear Effects</StatsReport_FromGear>

  <!-- Black Apple -->
  <XF_MessageBlackAppleInterest>{PAWN_labelShort} has been mentally infected by the black apple...</XF_MessageBlackAppleInterest>
  <XF_BlackAppleTurnedSpree>turn black apple</XF_BlackAppleTurnedSpree>
  <XF_BlackAppleTurnedSpreeDesc>{PAWN_labelShort} successfully turned the black apple, and the psychic infection finally ceased. However, those who had been affected by its psychic influence began to go mad due to the loss of connection, spewing curses and foul language incessantly. Those who were further away from the source of the infection became extremely sad, wandering around like zombies.</XF_BlackAppleTurnedSpreeDesc>
  <XF_BlackAppleTurnedSpreePawns>The following people started to curse others wildly due to the disruption of their psychic connection with the black apple.</XF_BlackAppleTurnedSpreePawns>
  <XF_BlackAppleTurnedCMPawns>The following people lost themselves due to the disruption of their psychic connection with the black apple.</XF_BlackAppleTurnedCMPawns>
  <XF_CannotTurnedBlackApple>{PAWN_labelShort} refuses to turn the black apple.</XF_CannotTurnedBlackApple>
  <XF_BlackAppleTurnConfirmation>Turn the black apple will cause all those affected by the psychic infection to curse others wildly, and any infected individuals in the caravan will lose themselves. However, more concerning than these effects, turning the black apple could potentially bring a nightmarish disaster to the colony.</XF_BlackAppleTurnConfirmation>
  <XF_BlackAppleTurnPawnsSpree>The following people will start cursing wildly</XF_BlackAppleTurnPawnsSpree>
  <XF_BlackAppleTurnPawnsCM>The following people will wander in sadness.</XF_BlackAppleTurnPawnsCM>
  <XF_BlackAppleTurnEnd>Are you sure you're ready?</XF_BlackAppleTurnEnd>

  <!-- Strange Ancient -->
  <XF_KillPXConfirmation>Telling the story of "Phoenix" to the strange ancient will lead to her death.</XF_KillPXConfirmation>
  <XF_KillPXEnd>Are you sure you want to do this?</XF_KillPXEnd>

  <!-- Visitors -->
  <XF_GroupVisitorsArrive>A group of people from {0} have discovered your colony and they have air-dropped some gifts to you. {1}{2}</XF_GroupVisitorsArrive>
  <XF_GroupVisitorsArriveLeaderInfo>\n\n{1_labelShort} is the leader of the group.</XF_GroupVisitorsArriveLeaderInfo>
  <XF_PawnJoined>{0} has joined the colony</XF_PawnJoined>
  <XF_PawnJoinedDesc>Because of {1}'s decision to join, {0} has chosen to join our colony alongside their beloved!</XF_PawnJoinedDesc>

  <!-- RSweapon -->
  <XF_WeaponLV>Weapon LV: </XF_WeaponLV>
  <XF_DamageM>\nDamage Multiplier: </XF_DamageM>

  <!-- MODsetup -->
  <XF_SAsongSetup>Enable Strange Ancient Singing Playback: </XF_SAsongSetup>
  <XF_SAsongDes>Turning off this option disables the playback of the strange ancient's singing. This only disables the playback; when she sings, it will still affect the creatures on the map, and changes will take effect at the start of the next cycle.</XF_SAsongDes>
  <XF_SAsongEffectSetup>Enable Strange Ancient Anomaly Effect: </XF_SAsongEffectSetup>
  <XF_SAsongEffectDes>Turning off this option disables the anomaly effects of the strange ancient. This only disables the effects; her singing will still be heard when she sings, and changes will take effect at the start of the next cycle.</XF_SAsongEffectDes>
  <XF_SAlevelIncrement>The level of the redstone weapon increases with each successful interaction (default value is 1): {0}</XF_SAlevelIncrement>
  <XF_WeaponDurabilityLoss>Weapon Durability Loss Toggle for Parry System:</XF_WeaponDurabilityLoss>
  <XF_WeaponDurabilityLossDes>When this option is disabled, weapons will no longer lose durability when triggering bullet deflection or parry.</XF_WeaponDurabilityLossDes>

</LanguageData>
