<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  
  <XFTTable.label>XF Tech Table</XFTTable.label>
  <XFTTable.description>Player can make stuff of Xeva Faction from this Table. (Except for disposable weapons and Black Market equipment.)</XFTTable.description>

  <XFModTable.label>XF Weapon Modification Table</XFModTable.label>
  <XFModTable.description>Some Xeva Faction weapons can be modified on this table. The modified weapons will only meet the needs, but they will not be stronger than the original weapons, and their quality will fluctuate.</XFModTable.description>

  <SculptureXSPX.label>Giant Sculpture - Phoenix</SculptureXSPX.label>
  <SculptureXSPX.description>The exploration team brought back a stunningly beautiful girl from an ancient ruin. She had a gem embedded on her forehead, which seemed to have affected her brain, causing her to babble about the infiltration of the mechanical race like a crazy person. She even had the habit of using Luciferium, causing a lot of trouble. The village chief did not want to take her in and scolded the captain for bringing her back. However, the captain insisted that the girl had saved their lives by rescuing them from the Mechanoid, so they owed her a debt of gratitude.

The captain was a handsome young man who was previously the target of the village chief's pursuit. Now that he was defending the girl, it made the chief even more unhappy. They went from discussing to arguing until the captain agreed to assign the girl to the combat unit, and the argument finally came to an end. The village chief knew that the girl's abilities were poor, with only outstanding close combat skills, and she was practically useless. So he deliberately assigned her to the frontline combat personnel, where it would be easy to get rid of her with just one command, and no one would say anything.

In the eyes of the village chief, this stunning beauty was not a good thing. The village quickly became embroiled in controversy because of her, but it wasn't because of her looks. It was because of that Luciferium. The villagers argued about the problems that hoarding these drugs would cause. The captain and some others continued to make excuses for her, seemingly enchanted by the girl, insisting on keeping those drugs for her. The village chief saw the girl as the root of chaos and knew that if left unchecked, it would surely lead to disaster. He believed it was time to get rid of her. 

Afterwards, the village chief began to assign the girl to deal with attacks, but every time she managed to survive, leaving the village chief with a headache. Until one day, the girl repeatedly warned the crowd of a Mechanoid attack. People thought she was going crazy from not having enough drugs and locked her up. But soon after, a Mechanoid cluster really did come near the village, blocking the transportation route. Everyone was at a loss, so they had no choice but to set up a killing ground in the village to deal with these monsters. Knowing that the girl could run fast, the village chief ordered her to be the bait.

The girl took out the equipment collected from ancient ruins and followed the village chief's instructions to lure the Mechanoids near the village. However, upon seeing their numbers, which exceeded the village's expectations, the chief became frightened and ordered the gates to be closed. The girl realized that she was trapped outside with no reinforcements, and although she could escape, leaving the villagers behind would put them in danger.

The people inside the walls were worried when they learned of the failed plan. The captain requested breaking through the enemy lines, but the village chief refused, citing the safety of the villagers. Seeing that the chances of success were slim, the captain did not insist further. The decision to defend the city was a reluctant one; tonight might be the village's last night on the map.

Feeling conflicted, the captain deployed his troops and walked up to the city wall alone, praying for a miracle. Suddenly, gunshots and explosions rang out from outside. The captain called out to his fighters, and curious villagers came to see what was happening. They saw the girl leading the Mechanoids through the woods, followed closely by gunfire and exploding wood. It was a spectacular sight.

Seeing this opportunity, the captain ignored the village chief's instructions and led his troops out of the gate to attack the Mechanoids. Under the girl's guidance and their own firepower, the Mechanoids fell one by one until they were all destroyed. The resulting fire burned down the forest, and thick smoke obscured the girl's figure. The villagers rushed to extinguish the flames and were relieved to see the girl walking out of the blaze unscathed. Everyone cheered, and the village chief praised her for being like a phoenix, rising from the ashes. This nickname quickly spread throughout the village.

After experiencing this miracle, the words spoken by the girl began to be accepted by people. She told the villagers about the Creator and recounted how her own tribe had been swallowed up and assimilated by the Mechanoids. She hoped that humanity could unite to face the Mechanoids. People became aware of the horrors of the Mechanoids through her and learned of the existence of the Creator. The villagers believed that saving the girl was not accidental, but because they were chosen by the Creator.

The girl became the guardian deity of the village and people learned from her. Some even consumed Luciferium to strengthen themselves, forming a combat unit to resist the Mechanoids. After that, the girl led the unit to help neighboring communities and absorbed those in need. Their reputation grew quickly, and the organization became more powerful. During this time, the captain and the girl fell in love, and the villagers held the grandest wedding in the village's history for them.

However, all of this seemed like a fleeting illusion. Since the defense battle, the village chief had been depressed and ignored by the masses, losing his authority and becoming an empty leader. Eventually, even his beloved man was taken away from him. The village chief lost everything due to the Phoenix and developed evil thoughts, planning a series of terrible things. 

At that time, the village had already become urbanized, with a large population of people with different ideologies. Taking advantage of his knowledge of human nature, the manipulative village chief visited vulnerable groups in the area and conveyed messages of equality in the name of the creator. Many oppressed crowds and slaves who heard this ideology came to the Phoenix for help. However, both the Phoenix and the captain were simple-minded and did not know how to handle these appeals. Ultimately, their good intentions and hesitation led to the situation spiraling out of control. Under the leadership of the masses, the organization began launching sub-missions to attack those in power, which further attracted the attention of many powerful figures.

One day, the base received a distress signal from the ancient ruins where a research team had found a Phoenix. The village chief believed it was related to the Mechanoids and requested that the captain investigate personally. He also ordered the Phoenix to bring along her troops for protection. Without suspecting any foul play, they set out on their journey. After they entered the ruins, they realized that things were not right. However, it was already too late. Dozens of drop pods instantly crashed through the ceiling, raining down like a fiery storm. The Mechanoids emerged from those metal canisters and surged towards them like a tsunami. Phoenix knew that they couldn't hold their position and ordered her troops to break through. However, the cramped indoor space caused a bottleneck, and soon they were surrounded. They had no choice but to fight to the death.

The number gap between the two sides was enormous, and Phoenix knew this was an unwinnable battle. All she could do was try her best to create openings within the swarm of machines, giving her troops a slim chance at survival. However, these Mechanoids seemed to know what she was thinking, and they quickly filled in any gaps she created. She had no chance. As she watched her team members fall one by one, even the captain being torn apart in front of her eyes, she finally gave up. Exhausted and defeated, she knelt down holding onto her blade. A Scyther approached her. Its hive mind recognized her as the woman who fought against them. Instead of simply executing her, the Scyther cruelly dismembered her, as if these machines also possessed "wrath". Even after Phoenix lost the battle, the fight continued for a long time. The ruins were almost leveled by them, and in the end, the Mechanoids emerged victorious. These cold-blooded machines spared no human present in the vicinity.

Pirates and raiders from different factions were drawn to the intense battle, constantly lurking in the distance to seize equipment and glass steel from the corpses. After the war, the number of Mechanoids dwindled, and the raiders took advantage of the opportunity to attack. The remaining Mechanoids were no match for them and were quickly destroyed after resisting for only a moment. These people scrambled over the corpses, dismantling the machines and taking everything they could get their hands on. Although these looters were all insane, none dared touch the body of Phoenix because they believed in the existence of the Creator and feared being cursed.

Until a young man appeared who became interested in the jewel on the forehead of the Phoenix. Without belief, he picked up a hammer and smashed her skull without hesitation, then pulled out the jewel and showed it off to the crowd. Witnessing this, fear instantly turned into greed and they began fighting over the jewel. The commanders of each faction saw what was happening and ordered them to stop. One of them told the people to look down at their feet, where they saw the young man lying dead in the chaos. At that moment, everyone came to their senses and no one dared touch the jewel again. This could have been a coincidence or the curse of the Creator; there is no conclusion. However, it is certain that nobody wanted to give it up, nor did anyone want to possess it. In the end, they decided to sell the jewel to the nobles and evenly distribute the money.

A few days later, the research team returned to their base with the carcass of the Phoenix. They claimed that the Phoenix was a spy from a higher race, but the crowd did not believe them. When they learned of the deaths of the Phoenix and the troops, they became furious and caused a riot at the base. To calm down the angry crowd, the village chief decided to expel all the scientists and scholars, and blamed the nobles who supported the research for the incident. The village chief regained power in this event, and was inspired by the crowds who believed in the Creator. From that day on, the village chief used the name of the Creator to establish various doctrines for the organization, and selected three others to form the Elder Council to manage the people. The organization's goal shifted from the Mechanoid to those who abused their power. From then on, the Elder Council and the organization were bound by the doctrines, threatening the nobles who abused their power while searching for the jewel on the Phoenix's head - the Black Apple.

The village chief fabricated everything about the XEO, and it's uncertain whether a creator truly exists. However, the emergence and demise of the immortal Phoenix gave birth to an organization that opposes tyranny. They act as watchdogs, bringing balance to the world in their own enigmatic way - this may well be the elusive modus operandi of the Creator.</SculptureXSPX.description>

  <SculptureXSFW.label>Giant Sculpture - Free Will</SculptureXSFW.label>
  <SculptureXSFW.description>Twin Star is an organization that emerged after the Pirate King crisis. At the time, the Pirate King completely ignored the threat posed by the XEO assassins with their powerful armed forces, and multiple failed assassination attempts highlighted the weaknesses of the XEO's ideology. Although the crisis was ultimately resolved due to internal turmoil among the pirates, it made the Star Explorer realize that maintaining balance cannot rely solely on brute force. Therefore, they established the Twin Star organization, which focuses on intelligence gathering. Twin Star and XEO are two opposing forces with different approaches to prevent power imbalances. While XEO uses direct intimidation and threats, Twin Star guides the powers to mutually constrain each other.

Due to the impact of the Pirate King's turmoil, the Star Explorer employed a very radical approach when establishing Twin Star. They automatically included twins born into the plan, rewriting their birth records and giving them a shared identity. From a young age, they underwent strict training and ideological education, believing themselves to be two halves of a whole. Even if one disappears, the "self" still exists, which they call the twin consciousness. These double life spies made counterintelligence agencies very headache-inducing. If only one is assassinated or captured, the other will continue the mission, and agencies would risk exposing their intelligence sources. Moreover, due to the twin consciousness, it is impossible to extract information from these individuals or make them betray their cause.

Twin Star had achieved great success for the Star Explorer using this unique advantage, but this inhumane practice had always been questioned. Eventually, the Star Explorer Council passed a bill prohibiting their continued use of twins, and Twin Star was subsequently replaced by other organizations within the Star Explorer. However, their ideals still exist, and those exiled by the Star Explorer, including the birth of the Flame Legion, are actually related to Twin Star.</SculptureXSFW.description>

  <SculptureXSGL.label>Giant Sculpture - King of Pirate</SculptureXSGL.label>
  <SculptureXSGL.description>A group of explorers returned to the city with their mules loaded with goods, their steps heavy. The lord of the city went out to meet them, both to congratulate them and to see his fiancée whom he hadn't seen for more than ten days. "Darling! Look at these, are you shocked?" The lord's fiancée was a tomb raider, and she seemed very excited as if she had just found treasure. "Honey, where did you get these?" The lord scanned the goods, which although not many, were all valuable. "An old pirate gave me some information that led me to these." The tomb raider looked very proud. "Is there anything special?" The lord was puzzled. "Are you stupid? Look at that set of golden armor, it's the legendary treasure of the Pirate King!" The tomb raider deliberately raised her voice. The lord knew that this woman had been fascinated by the legend of the Pirate King since she was young, and she had been clamoring to go explore every few days. Although each time she spent more than she gained, the lord liked her and couldn't help but indulge her. "Great! Anyway, unload the goods in the city first." The lord agreed, thinking that there was no way the treasure of the Pirate King would be found by such a small-time thief.

They were sorting through the goods in the warehouse when the tomb raider shouted for the lord to put on the golden armor so she could see it. The lord had no choice but to comply, but he didn't understand how the armor worked and just started pressing buttons randomly. Suddenly, a secret compartment opened, and a gemstone rolled out, immediately catching everyone's attention. The crowd started discussing and speculating about it, mentioning things like Black Apple and Creator, leaving the lord curious. He checked  wealth value of city and was stunned. "What the hell is this?" The lord blamed the tomb raider. "Maybe this is the legendary ONE PIECE!" The tomb raider dismissed it as a joke and her eyes sparkled with excitement. The lord was annoyed with the gemstone and his fiancée's careless response, so he spoke sternly, "Honey! It seems like you've been reading too many comics and trying to kill us!" "Darling! You asked me, and that's my answer." The tomb raider was dissatisfied and added an offensive gesture.

"Honey! Your head is full of holy shit!" The city lord immediately exploded with rage, drew out his plasteel longsword and swung it at the tomb raider. The tomb raider cowered in fear, but suddenly, the city lord froze. The tomb raider cowered in fear, but suddenly, the city lord froze. Everything came to a halt as a terrifying odor emanated from CPU-0. The few minutes of pause allowed the city lord to regain his senses. He helped his fiancée up and held her tightly, saying, "I'm sorry, it looks like neither of us will survive today..."</SculptureXSGL.description>

  <SculptureXSSA.label>Giant Sculpture - Wilderness Lover</SculptureXSSA.label>
  <SculptureXSSA.description>For the past few days, Vic and XvA have been lost in the wilderness. The vast plain before them seems never-ending, with no visible end in sight. The caravan map is useless in their current situation of being unable to determine their location.

Vic has never been so desperate for someone to attack them, just so he can loot some supplies. Their food is running out quickly and it weighs heavily on his mind. He hopes to find a settlement or come across another caravan before they run out of food completely. However, XvA and Vic have different reactions. XvA is not as stressed about the shortage of food. Ever since they brought along the Muffalo, her mood has improved significantly. She only read about these creatures in books before, never imagining that she would actually have one herself now.

Due to the Muffalo's enormous size, XvA can lie on top of it completely. She named the Muffalo "Papa" after this behavior. As Vic watches their bond deepen, he feels that something needs to be said. There are matters that he must clear up with XvA.

One day, Vic took the opportunity to talk to XvA. He advised her not to become too attached to Papa because they might have to eat him someday. XvA naively replied, "Brother, did you know that our creator looks like a Muffalo? Papa will find us food.""Actually, that's not the case at all. Just look around you at this barren wilderness. If you keep going down this path, you'll only suffer more," Vic spoke seriously to XvA. However, his words did not sway her. She was already too deeply attached to Papa and couldn't let him go.

Despite this, Vic gained inspiration from their conversation. Since Papa had traveled with caravans before, maybe he could lead them back to the right path. Vic decided to give it a try and let Papa walk on his own. He walked behind Papa and patted him on the rear. Papa carried XvA while making a "Puff Puff" sound as they walked. After a few hours of walking, Papa suddenly stopped and mooed towards the sky. Vic ran up to see what was going on and saw XvA patting Papa's head in praise. It turned out that Papa had found a wild berry bush. "Amazing... Papa found berries," XvA said in amazement. Vic was astonished to see that Papa had an ability to find berries. He also patted Papa's forehead to show his appreciation.

A few more days passed, and their supplies were completely depleted. They relied solely on Papa's unique ability to fend off hunger, but even with his help, the wild berries were too scarce and insufficient for them all. In their search for food, they had lost their way and had no idea where they were. Vic knew that if they continued like this, both he and XvA would perish. He remembered Zeo's words, "When it's time to be ruthless, you have to be." At this point, Vic felt that he had no other choice. He made the difficult decision to slaughter Papa and prepare him as a steak dinner.

That night, Vic waited until XvA fell asleep before approaching Papa with a gun. He hoped to end things quickly and relieve him of any pain. However, Papa noticed him and gently nudged his head against Vic while emitting a low rumbling sound. XvA woke up and saw the gun, realizing what was about to happen. She hugged Papa and burst into tears. Although XvA may not be the sharpest, she knew that this day would come sooner or later. Vic looked at her tear-streaked face and then back at Papa. He realized that he had subconsciously considered Papa as a part of their group ever since they escaped from the market. Vic also knew that his chances of survival were slim and that he was just barely holding on. In the end, he couldn't bring himself to pull the trigger. Instead, he removed Papa's equipment and patted him goodbye, allowing him to return to the wilderness. It was a moment of reckoning for Vic, and he was grateful that he didn't succumb to his inner demons as the guilt would have been too much to bear in his final moments.

After losing Papa, Vic abandoned all of their supplies except for a few medical kits. He joked with XvA, "Hey, we have nothing now, just empty stomachs." However, when he noticed XvA's strange expression and reddened cheeks, he became uneasy and worried that he had done something wrong. Suddenly, he saw a yellow loading bar appear beneath XvA, and she began to take off her clothes. "Stop! What are you doing?" Vic shouted. "I'm trying to help you…fill your hunger," XvA replied shyly. "Are you crazy?! Stop it!" Vic was shocked by the sudden turn of events. "Isn't this how men and women in a movies do it?" XvA asked innocently. "What kind of movies are you watching?" Vic retorted. "The RJW love-action series," XvA answered without hesitation, revealing her true colors as an experienced driver. Vic rolled his eyes and said, "You're still energetic even though you're hungry. I don't want to die yet." Despite XvA's confession being rejected by Vic, her mood remained unaffected. However, Vic couldn't shake off his feelings about the black stone incident. If he hadn't approached XvA that day, they wouldn't be in this predicament. Was this the unfortunate ending that the black stone had brought upon them?

The next day, they walked for half a day again, and both of them finally couldn't bear the hunger anymore. They sat down on the ground, with XvA already learning to eat grass while crawling. Vic tried to stop her, but at that moment, he looked at XvA's thighs and felt an inexplicable appetite rising inside him. It took him great effort to suppress it. Vic didn't know what was happening to himself and all that remained was a sense of fear and unease in his mind. Eventually, they both lay on the ground, waiting for the reaper's harvest. In their despair, a sound came from afar...</SculptureXSSA.description>

</LanguageData>