<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <XF_BionicEye.label>Sculptor Bionic Eye</XF_BionicEye.label>
  <XF_BionicEye.labelNoun>a Sculptor Bionic Eye</XF_BionicEye.labelNoun>
  <XF_BionicEye.description>The Sculptor Bionic Eye is a revolutionary bionic vision organ, featuring ultra-high-resolution vision, advanced infrared and ultraviolet perception, and dynamic target tracking. Its appearance is indistinguishable from a human eye, even mimicking pupil responses to light, seamlessly integrating with the body.</XF_BionicEye.description>
  
  <XF_BionicArm.label>Sculptor Bionic Arm</XF_BionicArm.label>
  <XF_BionicArm.labelNoun>a Sculptor Bionic Arm</XF_BionicArm.labelNoun>
  <XF_BionicArm.description>The Sculptor Bionic Arm combines unmatched strength and flexibility, with a nanoscale servo system for precise control of every movement. Its appearance mimics human skin and muscle texture, feeling warm and natural.</XF_BionicArm.description>
  <XF_BionicArm.comps.HediffComp_VerbGiver.tools.fist.label>fist</XF_BionicArm.comps.HediffComp_VerbGiver.tools.fist.label>
  
  <XF_BionicLeg.label>Sculptor Bionic Leg</XF_BionicLeg.label>
  <XF_BionicLeg.labelNoun>Sculptor Bionic Leg</XF_BionicLeg.labelNoun>
  <XF_BionicLeg.description>The Sculptor Bionic Leg employs advanced kinetic energy recovery and reinforced structural design, offering exceptional speed and stability. Its appearance perfectly mimics a human leg, with flawless details down to hair and skin texture.</XF_BionicLeg.description>
  
  <XF_BionicSpine.label>Sculptor Bionic Spine</XF_BionicSpine.label>
  <XF_BionicSpine.labelNoun>Sculptor Bionic Spine</XF_BionicSpine.labelNoun>
  <XF_BionicSpine.description>The Sculptor Bionic Spine is a groundbreaking bionic spine with built-in neural enhancement modules, significantly boosting reaction speed and physical coordination. Its appearance is indistinguishable from a real spine, seamlessly integrating with the body.</XF_BionicSpine.description>

  <XF_BionicHeart.label>Sculptor Bionic Heart</XF_BionicHeart.label>
  <XF_BionicHeart.labelNoun>Sculptor Bionic Heart</XF_BionicHeart.labelNoun>
  <XF_BionicHeart.description>The Sculptor Bionic Heart is a high-performance bionic heart with adaptive blood flow regulation and energy optimization, greatly enhancing endurance and recovery speed. Its appearance matches a real heart, even mimicking natural heartbeat rhythms.</XF_BionicHeart.description>

  <XF_BionicStomach.label>Sculptor Bionic Stomach</XF_BionicStomach.label>
  <XF_BionicStomach.labelNoun>Sculptor Bionic Stomach</XF_BionicStomach.labelNoun>
  <XF_BionicStomach.description>The Sculptor Bionic Stomach uses advanced nanodecomposition technology to efficiently process various foods and nutrients, even breaking down low-quality or toxic substances. Its appearance is identical to a real stomach, with a natural feel.</XF_BionicStomach.description>

  <XF_BionicEar.label>Sculptor Bionic Ear</XF_BionicEar.label>
  <XF_BionicEar.labelNoun>Sculptor Bionic Ear</XF_BionicEar.labelNoun>
  <XF_BionicEar.description>The Sculptor Bionic Ear is an ultra-sensitive auditory organ with wide-frequency sound capture and directional noise cancellation, capable of precisely identifying faint sounds from a distance. Its appearance is indistinguishable from a human ear, with perfectly replicated details.</XF_BionicEar.description>

  <XF_BionicTongue.label>Sculptor Bionic Tongue</XF_BionicTongue.label>
  <XF_BionicTongue.labelNoun>Sculptor Bionic Tongue</XF_BionicTongue.labelNoun>
  <XF_BionicTongue.description>The Sculptor Bionic Tongue features high-precision taste and chemical analysis modules, capable of identifying complex chemical compositions and flavors. Its appearance matches a real tongue, with natural moisture and elasticity.</XF_BionicTongue.description>

  <XF_BionicJaw.label>Sculptor Bionic Jaw</XF_BionicJaw.label>
  <XF_BionicJaw.labelNoun>Sculptor Bionic Jaw</XF_BionicJaw.labelNoun>
  <XF_BionicJaw.description>The Sculptor Bionic Jaw combines immense biting strength with precise motion control, featuring reinforced bone structure. Its appearance is identical to a human jaw, with lifelike teeth and muscle texture.</XF_BionicJaw.description>

  <XF_BionicLung.label>Sculptor Bionic Lung</XF_BionicLung.label>
  <XF_BionicLung.labelNoun>Sculptor Bionic Lung</XF_BionicLung.labelNoun>
  <XF_BionicLung.description>The Sculptor Bionic Lung is a high-performance respiratory organ with a mechanized design, featuring a stark metallic and synthetic aesthetic distinctly different from human lungs. Equipped with advanced gas filtration and oxygen optimization systems, it provides stable oxygen supply in extreme environments and filters toxic gases, far surpassing traditional bionic lungs.</XF_BionicLung.description>

  <XF_BionicKidney.label>Sculptor Bionic Kidney</XF_BionicKidney.label>
  <XF_BionicKidney.labelNoun>Sculptor Bionic Kidney</XF_BionicKidney.labelNoun>
  <XF_BionicKidney.description>The Sculptor Bionic Kidney features a mechanized structure with a precise metallic module and transparent conduit design, starkly contrasting human kidneys. Equipped with a nanoscale filtration system, it efficiently removes toxins and waste from the blood and includes self-regulating functions to adapt to varying metabolic needs, outperforming traditional bionic kidneys.</XF_BionicKidney.description>

  <XF_BionicNerve.label>Sculptor HyperSense Nerve</XF_BionicNerve.label>
  <XF_BionicNerve.labelNoun>a Sculptor HyperSense Nerve</XF_BionicNerve.labelNoun>
  <XF_BionicNerve.description>The Sculptor HyperSense Nerve is an advanced bionic neural layout, indistinguishable from the human nervous system in appearance, seamlessly integrating with the body. Equipped with overclocked neural conduction modules, it significantly enhances overall physical performance and reaction speed, enabling unparalleled agility and coordination in high-intensity activities.</XF_BionicNerve.description>

</LanguageData>