<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <XF_Fool.degreeDatas.0.label>Fool</XF_Fool.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <XF_Fool.degreeDatas.0.description>{PAWN_nameDef} doesn't seem very intelligent. {PAWN_pronoun} has a magical way of thinking, is slow to learn, and is easily persuaded by others. Nevertheless, fools always seem to find happiness more easily.</XF_Fool.degreeDatas.0.description>

  <XTRedScorpio.degreeDatas.0.label>&lt;color=#ff0000&gt;Red Scorpio&lt;/color&gt;</XTRedScorpio.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <XTRedScorpio.degreeDatas.0.description>There was once an infamous assassin, well known for her mastery in swordsmanship and her ghostly moves, a nightmare to all those nobles and bigwigs. By earning the title means that [PAWN_nameDef] has perfected the melee skill.</XTRedScorpio.degreeDatas.0.description>
  
  <XTTheQueen.degreeDatas.0.label>&lt;color=#ff0000&gt;Queen&lt;/color&gt;</XTTheQueen.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <XTTheQueen.degreeDatas.0.description>There was a saying about a sniper who was reluctant to kill so she aim for the knee everytime, and thus she was called The Queen. [PAWN_nameDef] can earn this title which means that [PAWN_possessive] shooting skill must has been proven many times.</XTTheQueen.degreeDatas.0.description>
  
  <XTDragon.degreeDatas.0.label>&lt;color=#ff0000&gt;Dragon&lt;/color&gt;</XTDragon.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <XTDragon.degreeDatas.0.description>There was once a warrior who encounter 13 knights all by his own and later become the leader of reble and leading it's army invaded the kingdom, thus , getting the name Dragon. [PAWN_nameDef] can win this title, means that [PAWN_possessive] battle skill is remarkable.</XTDragon.degreeDatas.0.description>
  
  <XTEvilGunner.degreeDatas.0.label>&lt;color=#ff0000&gt;Evil Gunner&lt;/color&gt;</XTEvilGunner.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <XTEvilGunner.degreeDatas.0.description>There was a legend of a SWAT whose gun kata was tricky and deadly like a devil, therefore got the name Evil Gunner. [PAWN_nameDef] can earn this title means that [PAWN_possessive] battle skill was outstanding.</XTEvilGunner.degreeDatas.0.description>
  
  <XTVirtuousDoctor.degreeDatas.0.label>&lt;color=#ff0000&gt;Virtuous Doctor&lt;/color&gt;</XTVirtuousDoctor.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <XTVirtuousDoctor.degreeDatas.0.description>Once a revengeful designer with gifts, after shooting his first love right in her head, he is now a doctor devoted into charity in order to redeem himself. [PAWN_nameDef] with this title is meaning that [PAWN_nameDef] is gifted in medicne and craftsmanship.</XTVirtuousDoctor.degreeDatas.0.description>
  
  <XTEagleEye.degreeDatas.0.label>&lt;color=#ff0000&gt;Eagle Eye&lt;/color&gt;</XTEagleEye.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <XTEagleEye.degreeDatas.0.description>There was once a mad sniper called Eagle Eye who, by his extraordinary shooting skill, only aiming for others' genital organ. [PAWN_nameDef] can get this title means [PAWN_possessive] shooting skill is extraordinary.</XTEagleEye.degreeDatas.0.description>
  
  <XTTheScream.degreeDatas.0.label>&lt;color=#ff0000&gt;Scream&lt;/color&gt;</XTTheScream.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <XTTheScream.degreeDatas.0.description>Once there was a serial killer who was called the Scream, because of his extreme ugliness, he torture and killed many handsome people and crafted them into some kind of sickness art as a protest to the God. [PAWN_nameDef] must be a psychopath and really good at craftsmanship to earn this title.</XTTheScream.degreeDatas.0.description>
  
  <XTPirateLord.degreeDatas.0.label>&lt;color=#ff0000&gt;Pirate King&lt;/color&gt;</XTPirateLord.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <XTPirateLord.degreeDatas.0.description>There was once a pirate king who invade every planet and every faction that he feels like to. No one dare to stand and against him, however, there were seven warrior who challenged him. After a whole night of battle, the pirate lord was defeated. [PAWN_possessive] battle skill must be getting out of control to earn this title.</XTPirateLord.degreeDatas.0.description>

</LanguageData>